0	1	Biden	Biden	NNP	root	0	PERSON	 (ROOT (FRAG (FRAG (NP (NNP Biden))	0	5
0	2	Increasingly	increasingly	RB	advmod	3	O	 (FRAG (ADJP (RB Increasingly)	6	18
0	3	Likely	likely	RB	dep	1	O	 (RB Likely)	19	25
0	4	to	to	TO	mark	6	O	 (S (VP (TO to)	26	28
0	5	Be	be	VB	aux:pass	6	O	 (VP (VB Be)	29	31
0	6	Impeached	impeach	VBN	xcomp	3	O	 (VP (VBN Impeached)	32	41
0	7	if	if	IN	mark	9	O	 (SBAR (IN if)	42	44
0	8	Republicans	Republicans	NNPS	nsubj	9	ORGANIZATION	 (S (NP (NNPS Republicans))	45	56
0	9	Regain	regain	VBP	advcl	6	ORGANIZATION	 (VP (VBP Regain)	57	63
0	10	Control	control	NN	obj	9	ORGANIZATION	 (NP (NP (NN Control))	64	71
0	11	of	of	IN	case	12	ORGANIZATION	 (PP (IN of)	72	74
0	12	House	House	NNP	nmod	10	ORGANIZATION	 (NP (NNP House))))))))))))	75	80
0	13	in	in	IN	case	14	O	 (PP (IN in)	81	83
0	14	Midterms	Midterms	NNPS	obl	3	O	 (NP (NNPS Midterms)))))	84	92
0	15	What	what	WP	obl	18	O	 (SBARQ (WHNP (WP What))	94	98
0	16	would	would	MD	aux	18	O	 (SQ (MD would)	99	104
0	17	they	they	PRP	nsubj	18	O	 (NP (PRP they))	105	109
0	18	impeach	impeach	VB	parataxis	1	O	 (VP (VB impeach)	110	117
0	19	him	he	PRP	obj	18	O	 (NP (PRP him))	118	121
0	20	for	for	IN	case	15	O	 (PP (IN for)))))	122	125
0	21	?	?	.	punct	1	O	 (. ?)))	125	126

