0	1	DeSantis	DeSantis	NNP	nsubj	2	PERSON	 (ROOT (S (NP (NNP DeSantis))	0	8
0	2	rejects	reject	VBZ	root	0	O	 (VP (VBZ rejects)	9	16
0	3	Biden	Biden	NNP	nmod:poss	5	PERSON	 (NP (NP (NP (NNP Biden)	17	22
0	4	’s	’s	POS	case	3	O	 (POS ’s))	22	24
0	5	request	request	NN	obj	2	O	 (NN request))	25	32
0	6	for	for	IN	case	9	O	 (PP (IN for)	33	36
0	7	Florida	Florida	NNP	compound	9	ORGANIZATION	 (NP (NP (NNP Florida)	37	44
0	8	National	National	NNP	compound	9	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP National)	45	53
0	9	Guard	Guard	NNP	nmod	5	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP Guard))	54	59
0	10	at	at	IN	case	11	O	 (PP (IN at)	60	62
0	11	State	State	NNP	nmod	9	O	 (NP (NP (NNP State))	63	68
0	12	of	of	IN	case	17	O	 (PP (IN of)	69	71
0	13	the	the	DT	det	17	O	 (NP (DT the)	72	75
0	14	Union	Union	NNP	compound	15	O	 (NML (NNP Union)	76	81
0	15	Jojo	Jojo	NNP	compound	17	PERSON	 (NNP Jojo))	83	87
0	16	lick	lick	NN	compound	17	O	 (NN lick)	88	92
0	17	peepee	peepee	NN	nmod	11	O	 (NN peepee))))))))	93	99
0	18	for	for	IN	case	20	O	 (PP (IN for)	100	103
0	19	for	for	IN	case	20	O	 (PP (IN for)	104	107
0	20	yumyum	yumyum	NN	obl	2	O	 (NP (NN yumyum)))))))	108	114

