0	1	Biden	Biden	NNP	nmod:poss	3	PERSON	 (ROOT (FRAG (FRAG (NP (NP (NNP Biden)	0	5
0	2	's	's	POS	case	1	O	 (POS 's))	5	7
0	3	Promise	Promise	NNP	root	0	O	 (NNP Promise))	8	15
0	4	to	to	IN	case	9	O	 (PP (IN to)	16	18
0	5	Nominate	Nominate	NNP	compound	9	ORGANIZATION	 (NP (NP (NNP Nominate)	19	27
0	6	A	A	NNP	compound	9	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP A)	28	29
0	7	Supreme	Supreme	NNP	compound	9	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP Supreme)	30	37
0	8	Court	Court	NNP	compound	9	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP Court)	38	43
0	9	Justice	Justice	NNP	obl	3	O	 (NNP Justice))	44	51
0	10	Based	base	VBN	case	12	O	 (PP (VBN Based)	52	57
0	11	on	on	IN	case	12	O	 (PP (IN on)	58	60
0	12	Sex	sex	NN	nmod	9	O	 (NP (NN Sex)))))))	61	64
0	13	,	,	,	punct	3	O	 (, ,)	64	65
0	14	Race	race	NN	parataxis	3	O	 (FRAG (FRAG (NP (NN Race))	66	70
0	15	Heavily	heavily	RB	advmod	16	O	 (ADVP (RB Heavily))	71	78
0	16	Criticized	criticize	VBN	dep	14	O	 (VP (VBN Criticized)	79	89
0	17	Y'	y'	NN	obj	16	O	 (NP (NN Y'))))	91	93
0	18	all	all	DT	nsubj	19	O	 (S (NP (DT all))	93	96
0	19	want	want	VBP	parataxis	14	O	 (VP (VBP want)	97	101
0	20	some	some	DT	det	21	O	 (NP (DT some)	102	106
0	21	cheese	cheese	NN	obj	19	O	 (NN cheese))	107	113
0	22	with	with	IN	case	25	O	 (PP (IN with)	114	118
0	23	all	all	PDT	det:predet	25	O	 (NP (PDT all)	119	122
0	24	that	that	DT	det	25	O	 (DT that)	123	127
0	25	whine	whine	NN	obl	19	O	 (NN whine))))))	128	133
0	26	?	?	.	punct	3	O	 (. ?)))	133	134

