0	1	CMV	cmv	NN	root	0	O	 (ROOT (FRAG (NP (NN CMV))	0	3
0	2	:	:	:	punct	1	O	 (: :)	3	4
0	3	Tucker	Tucker	NNP	compound	4	PERSON	 (S (NP (NP (NNP Tucker)	5	11
0	4	Carlson	Carlson	NNP	nsubj	12	PERSON	 (NNP Carlson))	12	19
0	5	asking	ask	VBG	acl	4	O	 (VP (VBG asking)	20	26
0	6	for	for	IN	case	10	O	 (PP (IN for)	27	30
0	7	KBJ	KBJ	NNP	nmod:poss	10	ORGANIZATION	 (NP (NP (NNP KBJ)	31	34
0	8	's	's	POS	case	7	O	 (POS 's))	34	36
0	9	LSAT	lsat	NN	compound	10	O	 (NN LSAT)	37	41
0	10	score	score	NN	obl	5	O	 (NN score)))))	42	47
0	11	is	be	VBZ	cop	12	O	 (VP (VBZ is)	48	50
0	12	racist	racist	JJ	appos	1	O	 (ADJP (JJ racist)	51	57
0	13	Fucker	Fucker	NNP	compound	14	PERSON	 (SBAR (S (NP (NNP Fucker)	59	65
0	14	Carlson	Carlson	NNP	nsubj	17	PERSON	 (NNP Carlson))	66	73
0	15	is	be	VBZ	cop	17	O	 (VP (VBZ is)	74	76
0	16	a	a	DT	det	17	O	 (NP (NP (DT a)	77	78
0	17	piece	piece	NN	ccomp	12	O	 (NN piece))	79	84
0	18	of	of	IN	case	20	O	 (PP (IN of)	85	87
0	19	shit	shit	NN	compound	20	O	 (NP (NN shit)	88	92
0	20	racist	racist	NN	nmod	17	O	 (NN racist))))))))))))	93	99

