0	1	Aaron	Aaron	NNP	compound	2	PERSON	 (ROOT (S (NP (NP (NNP Aaron)	0	5
0	2	Rodgers	Rodgers	NNP	nsubj	8	PERSON	 (NNP Rodgers))	6	13
0	3	and	and	CC	cc	5	O	 (CC and)	14	17
0	4	the	the	DT	det	5	O	 (NP (DT the)	18	21
0	5	Packers	Packers	NNPS	conj	2	ORGANIZATION	 (NNPS Packers)))	22	29
0	6	can	can	MD	aux	8	O	 (VP (MD can)	30	33
0	7	still	still	RB	advmod	8	O	 (ADVP (RB still))	34	39
0	8	make	make	VB	root	0	O	 (VP (VB make)	40	44
0	9	it	it	PRP	obj	8	O	 (NP (PRP it))	45	47
0	10	to	to	IN	case	13	O	 (PP (IN to)	48	50
0	11	the	the	DT	det	13	O	 (NP (DT the)	51	54
0	12	Super	Super	NNP	compound	13	O	 (NNP Super)	55	60
0	13	Bowl	Bowl	NNP	obl	8	O	 (NNP Bowl)))	61	65
0	14	if	if	IN	mark	17	O	 (SBAR (IN if)	66	68
0	15	Mike	Mike	NNP	compound	16	PERSON	 (S (NP (NNP Mike)	69	73
0	16	Pence	Pence	NNP	nsubj	17	PERSON	 (NNP Pence))	74	79
0	17	has	have	VBZ	advcl	8	O	 (VP (VBZ has)	80	83
0	18	enough	enough	JJ	amod	19	O	 (NP (JJ enough)	84	90
0	19	courage	courage	NN	obj	17	O	 (NN courage)))))))	91	98
0	20	.	.	.	punct	8	O	 (. .)))	98	99

1	1	Lame	lame	JJ	amod	2	O	 (ROOT (UCP (NP (JJ Lame)	101	105
1	2	ass	ass	NN	root	0	O	 (NN ass))	106	109
1	3	liberal	liberal	JJ	amod	4	IDEOLOGY	 (NP (JJ liberal)	110	117
1	4	Antifa	antifa	NN	dep	2	LOCATION	 (NN Antifa))	118	124
1	5	and	and	CC	cc	8	O	 (CC and)	125	128
1	6	Fraudchi	Fraudchi	NNP	compound	8	O	 (FRAG (NP (NNP Fraudchi)	129	137
1	7	style	style	NN	compound	8	O	 (NN style)	138	143
1	8	smear	smear	NN	conj	2	O	 (NN smear)))	144	149
1	9	.	.	.	punct	8	O	 (. .)))	149	150

2	1	I	I	PRP	nsubj	2	O	 (ROOT (S (NP (PRP I))	151	152
2	2	hope	hope	VBP	root	0	O	 (VP (VBP hope)	153	157
2	3	you	you	PRP	nsubj:pass	5	O	 (SBAR (S (NP (PRP you))	158	161
2	4	are	be	VBP	aux:pass	5	O	 (VP (VBP are)	162	165
2	5	woke	wake	VBN	ccomp	2	O	 (VP (VBN woke)	166	170
2	6	enough	enough	RB	advmod	5	O	 (ADVP (RB enough))	171	177
2	7	to	to	TO	mark	8	O	 (S (VP (TO to)	178	180
2	8	see	see	VB	xcomp	5	O	 (VP (VB see)	181	184
2	9	what	what	WP	obj	12	O	 (SBAR (WHNP (WP what))	185	189
2	10	you	you	PRP	nsubj	11	O	 (S (NP (PRP you))	190	193
2	11	have	have	VBP	ccomp	8	O	 (VP (VBP have)	194	198
2	12	coming	come	VBG	xcomp	11	O	 (S (VP (VBG coming)	199	205
2	13	before	before	IN	mark	15	O	 (SBAR (IN before)	206	212
2	14	it	it	PRP	nsubj	15	O	 (S (NP (PRP it))	213	215
2	15	hits	hit	VBZ	advcl	12	O	 (VP (VBZ hits)	216	220
2	16	you	you	PRP	obj	15	O	 (NP (PRP you))))))))))))))))))	221	224
2	17	.	.	.	punct	2	O	 (. .)))	224	225

