0	1	Basketball	basketball	NN	compound	2	TITLE	 (ROOT (S (S (NP (NML (NN Basketball)	0	10
0	2	Player	player	NN	compound	4	TITLE	 (NN Player))	11	17
0	3	Royce	Royce	NNP	compound	4	PERSON	 (NNP Royce)	18	23
0	4	W.	W.	NNP	nsubj	5	PERSON	 (NNP W.))	24	26
0	5	Runs	run	VBZ	root	0	PERSON	 (VP (VBZ Runs)	27	31
0	6	for	for	IN	case	7	O	 (PP (IN for)	32	35
0	7	Congress	Congress	NNP	obl	5	ORGANIZATION	 (NP (NNP Congress)))))	36	44
0	8	,	,	,	punct	5	O	 (, ,)	44	45
0	9	Challenging	Challenging	NNP	compound	11	O	 (FRAG (NP (NNP Challenging)	46	57
0	10	Ilhan	Ilhan	NNP	compound	11	PERSON	 (NNP Ilhan)	58	63
0	11	Omar	Omar	NNP	parataxis	5	PERSON	 (NNP Omar))	64	68
0	12	amazing	amazing	JJ	dep	11	O	 (ADJP (JJ amazing))	70	77
0	13	i	i	PRP	nsubj	14	O	 (SBAR (S (NP (PRP i))	78	79
0	14	hope	hope	VBP	dep	11	O	 (VP (VBP hope)	80	84
0	15	he	he	PRP	nsubj	16	O	 (SBAR (S (NP (PRP he))	85	87
0	16	wins	win	VBZ	ccomp	14	O	 (VP (VBZ wins))))))))	88	92
0	17	.	.	.	punct	5	O	 (. .)))	92	93

1	1	she	she	PRP	nsubj	5	O	 (ROOT (S (NP (PRP she))	94	97
1	2	's	be	VBZ	cop	5	O	 (VP (VBZ 's)	97	99
1	3	literally	literally	RB	advmod	5	O	 (ADVP (RB literally))	100	109
1	4	a	a	DT	det	5	O	 (NP (NP (DT a)	110	111
1	5	terrorist	terrorist	NN	root	0	O	 (NN terrorist))	112	121
1	6	in	in	IN	mark	7	O	 (PP (IN in)	122	124
1	7	disguise	disguise	VB	acl	5	O	 (S (VP (VB disguise))))))	125	133
1	8	.	.	.	punct	5	O	 (. .)))	133	134

