0	1	Watch	watch	VB	root	0	O	 (ROOT (S (VP (VB Watch)	0	5
0	2	:	:	:	punct	1	O	 (: :)	5	6
0	3	Newt	Newt	NNP	compound	4	PERSON	 (S (NP (NNP Newt)	7	11
0	4	Gingrich	Gingrich	NNP	nsubj	5	PERSON	 (NNP Gingrich))	12	20
0	5	Says	say	VBZ	ccomp	1	O	 (VP (VBZ Says)	21	25
0	6	Jan.	Jan.	NNP	obl:tmod	5	DATE	 (NP-TMP (NNP Jan.)	26	30
0	7	6	6	CD	nummod	6	DATE	 (CD 6))	31	32
0	8	Committee	Committee	NNP	compound	9	ORGANIZATION	 (SBAR (S (NP (NNP Committee)	33	42
0	9	May	May	NNP	nsubj	10	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP May))	43	46
0	10	Face	face	VBP	ccomp	5	ORGANIZATION	 (VP (VBP Face)	47	51
0	11	Criminal	criminal	JJ	amod	12	ORGANIZATION	 (NP (NP (JJ Criminal)	52	60
0	12	Prosecution	prosecution	NN	obj	10	ORGANIZATION	 (NN Prosecution))	61	72
0	13	After	after	IN	case	14	O	 (PP (IN After)	73	78
0	14	Midterms	Midterms	NNPS	nmod	12	O	 (NP (NNPS Midterms))))	79	87
0	15	The	the	DT	det	16	O	 (NP-TMP (NP (DT The)	89	92
0	16	party	party	NN	obl:tmod	10	O	 (NN party))	93	98
0	17	of	of	IN	case	18	O	 (PP (IN of)	99	101
0	18	accountability	accountability	NN	nmod	16	O	 (NP (NN accountability)	102	116
0	19	and	and	CC	cc	20	O	 (CC and)	117	120
0	20	hypocrisy	hypocrisy	NN	conj	18	O	 (NN hypocrisy))))))))))	121	130
0	21	.	.	.	punct	1	O	 (. .)))	130	131

1	1	I	I	PRP	nsubj	2	O	 (ROOT (S (NP (PRP I))	132	133
1	2	wonder	wonder	VBP	root	0	O	 (VP (VBP wonder)	134	140
1	3	how	how	WRB	advmod	4	O	 (SBAR (WHADJP (WRB how)	141	144
1	4	many	many	JJ	dep	8	O	 (JJ many))	145	149
1	5	other	other	JJ	amod	6	O	 (S (NP (JJ other)	150	155
1	6	investigators	investigator	NNS	nsubj:pass	8	O	 (NNS investigators))	156	169
1	7	got	get	VBD	aux:pass	8	O	 (VP (VBD got)	170	173
1	8	thrown	throw	VBN	ccomp	2	O	 (VP (VBN thrown)	174	180
1	9	in	in	IN	case	10	O	 (PP (IN in)	181	183
1	10	jail	jail	NN	obl	8	O	 (NP (NN jail)))	184	188
1	11	for	for	IN	mark	12	O	 (PP (IN for)	189	192
1	12	looking	look	VBG	advcl	8	O	 (S (VP (VBG looking)	193	200
1	13	to	to	TO	mark	14	O	 (S (VP (TO to)	201	203
1	14	close	close	VB	xcomp	12	O	 (VP (VB close))))))))))))	204	209
1	15	.	.	.	punct	2	O	 (. .)))	209	210

