0	1	CMV	cmv	NN	root	0	O	 (ROOT (FRAG (NP (NN CMV))	0	3
0	2	:	:	:	punct	1	O	 (: :)	3	4
0	3	Tucker	Tucker	NNP	compound	4	PERSON	 (NP (NP (NNP Tucker)	5	11
0	4	Carlson	Carlson	NNP	dep	1	PERSON	 (NNP Carlson))	12	19
0	5	asking	ask	VBG	acl	4	O	 (VP (VBG asking)	20	26
0	6	for	for	IN	mark	12	O	 (SBAR (IN for)	27	30
0	7	KBJ	KBJ	NNP	nmod:poss	10	ORGANIZATION	 (S (NP (NP (NNP KBJ)	31	34
0	8	's	's	POS	case	7	O	 (POS 's))	34	36
0	9	LSAT	lsat	NN	compound	10	O	 (NN LSAT)	37	41
0	10	score	score	NN	nsubj	12	O	 (NN score))	42	47
0	11	is	be	VBZ	cop	12	O	 (VP (VBZ is)	48	50
0	12	racist	racist	JJ	advcl	5	O	 (ADJP (JJ racist)	51	57
0	13	100	100	CD	nummod	14	PERCENT	 (NP (CD 100)	59	62
0	14	%	%	NN	dep	12	PERCENT	 (NN %))))))))	62	63
0	15	.	.	.	punct	1	O	 (. .)))	63	64

1	1	He	he	PRP	nsubj	3	O	 (ROOT (S (NP (PRP He))	65	67
1	2	never	never	RB	advmod	3	O	 (ADVP (RB never))	68	73
1	3	asked	ask	VBD	root	0	O	 (VP (VBD asked)	74	79
1	4	for	for	IN	case	5	O	 (PP (IN for)	80	83
1	5	ACB	ACB	NNP	obl	3	ORGANIZATION	 (NP (NNP ACB)	84	87
1	6	's	's	POS	case	5	O	 (POS 's)))	87	89
1	7	,	,	,	punct	3	O	 (, ,)	89	90
1	8	or	or	CC	cc	11	O	 (NAC (CC or)	91	93
1	9	Kavenaughs	Kavenaughs	NNP	compound	11	LOCATION	 (NP (NNP Kavenaughs)	94	104
1	10	,	,	,	punct	11	O	 (, ,)	104	105
1	11	Gorseichs	Gorseichs	NNP	dep	3	PERSON	 (NNP Gorseichs))))	106	115
1	12	.	.	.	punct	3	O	 (. .)))	115	116

2	1	Tucker	Tucker	NNP	nsubj	5	PERSON	 (ROOT (S (NP (NNP Tucker))	117	123
2	2	is	be	VBZ	cop	5	O	 (VP (VBZ is)	124	126
2	3	a	a	DT	det	5	O	 (NP (NP (DT a)	127	128
2	4	raging	rage	VBG	amod	5	O	 (ADJP (VBG raging))	129	135
2	5	racist	racist	NN	root	0	O	 (NN racist)	136	142
2	6	and	and	CC	cc	7	O	 (CC and)	143	146
2	7	piece	piece	NN	conj	5	O	 (NN piece))	147	152
2	8	of	of	IN	case	9	O	 (PP (IN of)	153	155
2	9	filth	filth	NN	nmod	5	O	 (NP (NN filth)))))	156	161
2	10	.	.	.	punct	5	O	 (. .)))	161	162

