0	1	Fox	Fox	NNP	compound	2	MISC	 (ROOT (FRAG (NP (NNP Fox)	0	3
0	2	News	News	NNP	root	0	MISC	 (NNP News))	4	8
0	3	:	:	:	punct	2	O	 (: :)	8	9
0	4	Leaked	Leaked	NNP	compound	5	ORGANIZATION	 (NP (NP (NNP Leaked)	10	16
0	5	Kremlin	Kremlin	NNP	dep	2	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP Kremlin))	17	24
0	6	memo	memo	NN	nsubj	7	O	 (SBAR (S (NP (NN memo))	25	29
0	7	tells	tell	VBZ	acl:relcl	5	O	 (VP (VBZ tells)	30	35
0	8	Russian	russian	JJ	amod	9	NATIONALITY	 (NP (JJ Russian)	36	43
0	9	media	media	NNS	obj	7	O	 (NNS media))	44	49
0	10	to	to	TO	mark	11	O	 (S (VP (TO to)	50	52
0	11	feature	feature	VB	xcomp	7	O	 (VP (VB feature)	53	60
0	12	Tucker	Tucker	NNP	compound	14	PERSON	 (NP (NP (NNP Tucker)	61	67
0	13	Carlson	Carlson	NNP	compound	14	PERSON	 (NNP Carlson)	68	75
0	14	Redditors	Redditors	NNP	obj	11	PERSON	 (NNP Redditors))	77	86
0	15	calling	call	VBG	acl	14	O	 (VP (VBG calling)	87	94
0	16	for	for	IN	case	18	O	 (PP (IN for)	95	98
0	17	ethnic	ethnic	JJ	amod	18	CRIMINAL_CHARGE	 (NP (NP (JJ ethnic)	99	105
0	18	cleansing	cleansing	NN	obl	15	CRIMINAL_CHARGE	 (NN cleansing))	106	115
0	19	of	of	IN	case	20	O	 (PP (IN of)	116	118
0	20	Russians	Russians	NNPS	nmod	18	MISC	 (NP (NNPS Russians))))))))))))))	119	127
0	21	.	.	.	punct	2	O	 (. .)))	127	128

1	1	&	&	CC	cc	2	O	 (ROOT (FRAG (NP (NP (CC &)	130	131
1	2	#x200B	#x200b	NN	root	0	O	 (NN #x200B))	131	137
1	3	;	;	:	punct	2	O	 (: ;)	137	138
1	4	&	&	CC	cc	5	O	 (NP (CC &)	140	141
1	5	#x200B	#x200b	NN	dep	2	O	 (NN #x200B)))	141	147
1	6	;	;	:	punct	2	O	 (: ;)	147	148
1	7	Apologize	apologize	VB	parataxis	2	O	 (S (VP (VB Apologize)	150	159
1	8	right	right	RB	advmod	9	O	 (S (NP (RB right)	160	165
1	9	the	the	DT	nsubj	10	O	 (DT the))	166	169
1	10	fuck	fuck	VB	ccomp	7	O	 (VP (VB fuck)	170	174
1	11	now	now	RB	advmod	10	DATE	 (ADVP (RB now))))))	175	178
1	12	!	!	.	punct	2	O	 (. !)))	178	179

