0	1	GOP	GOP	NNP	compound	2	ORGANIZATION	 (ROOT (S (NP (NML (NNP GOP)	0	3
0	2	Rep.	Rep.	NNP	compound	4	TITLE	 (NNP Rep.))	4	8
0	3	Madison	Madison	NNP	compound	4	PERSON	 (NNP Madison)	9	16
0	4	Cawthorn	Cawthorn	NNP	nsubj	5	PERSON	 (NNP Cawthorn))	17	25
0	5	launches	launch	VBZ	root	0	O	 (VP (VBZ launches)	26	34
0	6	campaign	campaign	NN	obj	5	O	 (NP (NN campaign))	35	43
0	7	to	to	TO	mark	8	O	 (S (VP (TO to)	44	46
0	8	impose	impose	VB	advcl	5	O	 (VP (VB impose)	47	53
0	9	term	term	NN	compound	10	O	 (NP (NN term)	54	58
0	10	limits	limit	NNS	obj	8	O	 (NNS limits))	59	65
0	11	on	on	IN	case	12	O	 (PP (IN on)	66	68
0	12	Congress	Congress	NNP	obl	8	ORGANIZATION	 (NP (NNP Congress)))	69	77
0	13	:	:	:	punct	8	O	 (: :)	77	78
0	14	'	'	``	punct	8	O	 (`` ')	79	80
0	15	Drain	drain	VB	dep	8	O	 (VB Drain)	80	85
0	16	the	the	DT	det	30	O	 (NP (NP (DT the)	86	89
0	17	swamp	swamp	VB	compound	30	O	 (NML (S (VP (VB swamp)	90	95
0	18	'	'	``	punct	20	O	 (S (`` ')	95	96
0	19	I	I	PRP	nsubj	20	O	 (NP (PRP I))	98	99
0	20	guess	guess	VBP	ccomp	17	O	 (VP (VBP guess)	100	105
0	21	that	that	DT	nsubj	23	O	 (SBAR (S (NP (DT that))	106	110
0	22	might	might	MD	aux	23	O	 (VP (MD might)	111	116
0	23	help	help	VB	ccomp	20	O	 (VP (VB help)	117	121
0	24	remove	remove	VB	ccomp	23	O	 (S (VP (VB remove)	122	128
0	25	serial	serial	JJ	amod	27	O	 (NP (JJ serial)	129	135
0	26	sexual	sexual	JJ	amod	27	O	 (JJ sexual)	136	142
0	27	assaulters	assaulter	NNS	obj	24	O	 (NNS assaulters))	143	153
0	28	like	like	IN	case	29	O	 (PP (IN like)	154	158
0	29	Madison	Madison	NNP	obl	24	PERSON	 (NP (NNP Madison))))))))))))))	159	166
0	30	Cawthorn	Cawthorn	NNP	dep	8	PERSON	 (NNP Cawthorn))	167	175
0	31	from	from	IN	case	33	O	 (PP (IN from)	176	180
0	32	the	the	DT	det	33	O	 (NP (NP (DT the)	181	184
0	33	halls	hall	NNS	nmod	30	O	 (NNS halls))	185	190
0	34	of	of	IN	case	35	O	 (PP (IN of)	191	193
0	35	power	power	NN	nmod	33	O	 (NP (NN power))))))))))	194	199
0	36	.	.	.	punct	5	O	 (. .)))	199	200

