0	1	‘	‘	``	punct	19	O	 (ROOT (S (`` ‘)	0	1
0	2	Stop	stop	VB	ccomp	19	O	 (S (VP (VP (VB Stop)	1	5
0	3	Trying	try	VBG	xcomp	2	O	 (S (VP (VBG Trying)	6	12
0	4	To	to	TO	mark	5	O	 (S (VP (TO To)	13	15
0	5	Cancel	cancel	VB	xcomp	3	O	 (VP (VB Cancel)	16	22
0	6	People	people	NNS	obj	5	O	 (NP (NNS People)	23	29
0	7	’	’	POS	case	6	O	 (POS ’))))))))	29	30
0	8	:	:	:	punct	2	O	 (: :)	30	31
0	9	CNN	CNN	NNP	compound	10	ORGANIZATION	 (NP (NP (NNP CNN)	32	35
0	10	Host	host	NN	obj	2	ORGANIZATION	 (NN Host))	36	40
0	11	Don	Don	NNP	compound	12	ORGANIZATION	 (SBAR (S (NP (NNP Don)	41	44
0	12	Lemon	Lemon	NNP	nsubj	13	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP Lemon))	45	50
0	13	Accepts	accept	VBZ	acl:relcl	10	O	 (VP (VBZ Accepts)	51	58
0	14	Whoopi	Whoopi	NNP	compound	15	PERSON	 (NP (NP (NNP Whoopi)	59	65
0	15	Goldberg	Goldberg	NNP	nmod:poss	17	PERSON	 (NNP Goldberg)	66	74
0	16	’s	’s	POS	case	15	O	 (POS ’s))	74	76
0	17	Apology	apology	NN	obj	13	O	 (NN Apology))))))))	77	84
0	18	,	,	,	punct	19	O	 (, ,)	84	85
0	19	Urges	urge	VBZ	root	0	O	 (VP (VBZ Urges)	86	91
0	20	Forgiveness	forgiveness	NN	iobj	19	O	 (NP (NP (NN Forgiveness))	92	103
0	21	|	|	NFP	punct	20	O	 (NFP |)	104	105
0	22	The	the	DT	det	24	O	 (NP (NP (DT The)	106	109
0	23	Daily	Daily	NNP	compound	24	SET	 (NML (NNP Daily)	110	115
0	24	Wire	Wire	NNP	dep	20	O	 (NNP Wire)))	116	120
0	25	Oh	oh	UH	discourse	26	O	 (SBAR (S (VP (INTJ (UH Oh))	122	124
0	26	fuck	fuck	VB	acl:relcl	24	O	 (VB fuck)	125	129
0	27	him	he	PRP	obj	26	O	 (NP (PRP him))))))))	130	133
0	28	.	.	.	punct	19	O	 (. .)))	133	134

