0	1	CMV	cmv	NN	nsubj	12	O	 (ROOT (S (S (NP (NP (NN CMV))	0	3
0	2	:	:	:	punct	1	O	 (: :)	3	4
0	3	Tucker	Tucker	NNP	compound	4	PERSON	 (NP (NP (NNP Tucker)	5	11
0	4	Carlson	Carlson	NNP	dep	1	PERSON	 (NNP Carlson))	12	19
0	5	asking	ask	VBG	acl	4	O	 (VP (VBG asking)	20	26
0	6	for	for	IN	case	10	O	 (PP (IN for)	27	30
0	7	KBJ	KBJ	NNP	nmod:poss	10	ORGANIZATION	 (NP (NP (NNP KBJ)	31	34
0	8	's	's	POS	case	7	O	 (POS 's))	34	36
0	9	LSAT	lsat	NN	compound	10	O	 (NN LSAT)	37	41
0	10	score	score	NN	obl	5	O	 (NN score))))))	42	47
0	11	is	be	VBZ	cop	12	O	 (VP (VBZ is)	48	50
0	12	racist	racist	JJ	root	0	O	 (ADJP (JJ racist)	51	57
0	13	You	you	PRP	nsubj	17	O	 (SBAR (S (NP (PRP You))	59	62
0	14	could	could	MD	aux	17	O	 (VP (MD could)	63	68
0	15	have	have	VB	aux	17	O	 (VP (VB have)	69	73
0	16	just	just	RB	advmod	17	O	 (ADVP (RB just))	74	78
0	17	shorted	short	VBN	ccomp	12	O	 (VP (VBN shorted)	79	86
0	18	the	the	DT	det	19	O	 (PP (NP (DT the)	87	90
0	19	title	title	NN	obl	17	O	 (NN title))	91	96
0	20	to	to	IN	case	19	O	 (IN to))))))))))	97	99
0	21	:	:	:	punct	12	O	 (: :)	99	100
0	22	Tucker	Tucker	NNP	compound	23	PERSON	 (S (NP (NNP Tucker)	101	107
0	23	Carlson	Carlson	NNP	nsubj	26	PERSON	 (NNP Carlson))	108	115
0	24	is	be	VBZ	cop	26	O	 (VP (VBZ is)	116	118
0	25	a	a	DT	det	26	O	 (NP (DT a)	119	120
0	26	racist	racist	NN	parataxis	12	O	 (NN racist))))	122	128
0	27	.	.	.	punct	12	O	 (. .)))	128	129

