0	1	One	one	CD	nummod	2	NUMBER	 (ROOT (FRAG (S (NP (CD One)	0	3
0	2	Thing	thing	NN	nsubj	4	O	 (NN Thing))	4	9
0	3	to	to	TO	mark	4	O	 (VP (TO to)	10	12
0	4	Look	look	VB	root	0	O	 (VP (VB Look)	13	17
0	5	Forward	Forward	NNP	obj	4	O	 (NP (NNP Forward))	18	25
0	6	to	to	TO	advcl	4	O	 (S (VP (TO to))))))	26	28
0	7	If	if	IN	mark	9	O	 (S (SBAR (IN If)	29	31
0	8	GOP	GOP	NNP	nsubj	9	ORGANIZATION	 (S (NP (NNP GOP))	32	35
0	9	Takes	take	VBZ	advcl	27	O	 (VP (VBZ Takes)	36	41
0	10	Back	back	RB	advmod	16	O	 (PP (RB Back)	42	46
0	11	Majority	Majority	NNP	dep	14	O	 (S (NP (NML (NML (NNP Majority))	47	55
0	12	:	:	:	punct	14	O	 (: :)	55	56
0	13	Chairman	Chairman	NNP	compound	14	TITLE	 (NML (NNP Chairman)	57	65
0	14	Rand	Rand	NNP	compound	15	PERSON	 (NNP Rand)))	66	70
0	15	Paul	Paul	NNP	nsubj	16	PERSON	 (NNP Paul))	71	75
0	16	Investigating	investigate	VBG	advcl	9	PERSON	 (VP (VBG Investigating)	76	89
0	17	Fauci	Fauci	NNP	obj	16	PERSON	 (NP (NP (NNP Fauci))	90	95
0	18	what	what	WP	nsubj	19	O	 (SBAR (WHNP (WP what))	97	101
0	19	's	be	VBZ	acl:relcl	17	O	 (S (VP (VBZ 's)	101	103
0	20	to	to	TO	mark	21	O	 (S (VP (TO to)	104	106
0	21	investigate	investigate	VB	xcomp	19	O	 (VP (VB investigate))))))))))))))	107	118
0	22	,	,	,	punct	27	O	 (, ,)	118	119
0	23	his	he	PRP$	nmod:poss	25	O	 (NP (PRP$ his)	120	123
0	24	duplicitous	duplicitous	JJ	amod	25	O	 (JJ duplicitous)	124	135
0	25	incompetence	incompetence	NN	nsubj	27	O	 (NN incompetence))	136	148
0	26	is	be	VBZ	cop	27	O	 (VP (VBZ is)	149	151
0	27	manifest	manifest	JJ	parataxis	4	O	 (ADJP (JJ manifest))))))	152	160

