0	1	Donald	Donald	NNP	compound	2	PERSON	 (ROOT (S (S (NP (NNP Donald)	0	6
0	2	Trump	Trump	NNP	nsubj	4	PERSON	 (NNP Trump))	7	12
0	3	was	be	VBD	aux	4	O	 (VP (VBD was)	13	16
0	4	cozying	cozy	VBG	root	0	O	 (VP (VBG cozying)	17	24
0	5	up	up	RP	compound:prt	4	O	 (PRT (RP up))	25	27
0	6	to	to	IN	case	7	O	 (PP (IN to)	28	30
0	7	Putin	Putin	NNP	obl	4	PERSON	 (NP (NNP Putin)))	31	36
0	8	because	because	IN	mark	10	O	 (SBAR (SBAR (IN because)	37	44
0	9	Putin	Putin	NNP	nsubj	10	PERSON	 (S (S (NP (NNP Putin))	45	50
0	10	helped	help	VBD	advcl	4	O	 (VP (VBD helped)	51	57
0	11	get	get	VB	ccomp	10	O	 (S (VP (VB get)	58	61
0	12	him	he	PRP	nsubj	13	O	 (S (NP (PRP him))	62	65
0	13	elected	elect	VBN	dep	11	O	 (VP (VBN elected)))))))	66	73
0	14	and	and	CC	cc	16	O	 (CC and)	74	77
0	15	he	he	PRP	nsubj	16	O	 (S (NP (PRP he))	78	80
0	16	used	use	VBD	conj	10	O	 (VP (VBD used)	81	85
0	17	it	it	PRP	obj	16	O	 (NP (PRP it))	86	88
0	18	to	to	IN	case	21	O	 (PP (IN to)	89	91
0	19	blackmail	blackmail	NN	compound	21	CRIMINAL_CHARGE	 (NP (NN blackmail)	92	101
0	20	Donald	Donald	NNP	compound	21	PERSON	 (NNP Donald)	102	108
0	21	Trump	Trump	NNP	obl	16	PERSON	 (NNP Trump)))	109	114
0	22	to	to	TO	mark	23	O	 (S (VP (TO to)	115	117
0	23	start	start	VB	advcl	16	O	 (VP (VB start)	118	123
0	24	to	to	IN	case	26	O	 (PP (IN to)	124	126
0	25	exit	exit	NN	compound	26	O	 (NP (NN exit)	127	131
0	26	NATO	NATO	NNP	obl	23	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP NATO))))))))))	132	136
0	27	,	,	,	punct	10	O	 (, ,)	136	137
0	28	but	but	CC	cc	35	O	 (CC but)	138	141
0	29	when	when	WRB	advmod	35	O	 (SBAR (WHADVP (WRB when))	142	146
0	30	the	the	DT	det	32	O	 (S (NP (NP (DT the)	147	150
0	31	Pandemic	Pandemic	NNP	compound	32	O	 (NNP Pandemic)	151	159
0	32	hit	hit	NN	nsubj	35	O	 (NN hit))	160	163
0	33	,	,	,	punct	32	O	 (, ,)	163	164
0	34	Trump	Trump	NNP	appos	32	PERSON	 (NP (NNP Trump)))	165	170
0	35	fucked	fuck	VBD	conj	10	O	 (VP (VBD fucked)	171	177
0	36	up	up	RP	compound:prt	35	O	 (PRT (RP up))	178	180
0	37	even	even	RB	advmod	38	O	 (ADJP (RB even)	181	185
0	38	worse	worse	JJR	xcomp	35	O	 (JJR worse)))))))))	186	191
0	39	,	,	,	punct	4	O	 (, ,)	191	192
0	40	and	and	CC	cc	42	O	 (CC and)	193	196
0	41	Putin	Putin	NNP	nsubj	42	PERSON	 (S (NP (NNP Putin))	197	202
0	42	ran	run	VBD	conj	4	O	 (VP (VBD ran)	203	206
0	43	out	out	IN	compound:prt	42	O	 (PRT (IN out))	207	210
0	44	of	of	IN	case	45	O	 (PP (IN of)	211	213
0	45	time	time	NN	obl	42	O	 (NP (NP (NN time))	214	218
0	46	in	in	IN	acl	45	O	 (PP (IN in)	219	221
0	47	order	order	NN	fixed	46	O	 (NP (NN order)))))	222	227
0	48	to	to	TO	mark	49	O	 (S (VP (TO to)	228	230
0	49	invade	invade	VB	xcomp	42	O	 (VP (VB invade)	231	237
0	50	Ukraine	Ukraine	NNP	obj	49	COUNTRY	 (NP (NNP Ukraine))	238	245
0	51	without	without	IN	case	53	O	 (PP (IN without)	246	253
0	52	American	american	JJ	amod	53	NATIONALITY	 (NP (JJ American)	254	262
0	53	intervention	intervention	NN	obl	49	O	 (NN intervention))))))))	263	275
0	54	.	.	.	punct	4	O	 (. .)))	275	276

1	1	Hunter	Hunter	NNP	compound	2	PERSON	 (ROOT (FRAG (NP (NNP Hunter)	278	284
1	2	Biden	Biden	NNP	root	0	PERSON	 (NNP Biden))	285	290
1	3	a	a	DT	det	4	O	 (NP (DT a)	291	292
1	4	homosexual	homosexual	NN	dep	2	O	 (NN homosexual))))	293	303

