0	1	Florida	Florida	NNP	compound	2	STATE_OR_PROVINCE	 (ROOT (S (NP (NP (NNP Florida)	0	7
0	2	Governor	Governor	NNP	nmod:poss	5	TITLE	 (NNP Governor)	8	16
0	3	's	's	POS	case	2	O	 (POS 's))	16	18
0	4	Team	Team	NNP	compound	5	PERSON	 (NNP Team)	19	23
0	5	DeSantis	DeSantis	NNP	nsubj	6	PERSON	 (NNP DeSantis))	24	32
0	6	Launches	launch	VBZ	root	0	O	 (VP (VBZ Launches)	33	41
0	7	"	"	``	punct	11	O	 (NP (`` ")	42	43
0	8	DeSantis	DeSantis	NNP	compound	11	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP DeSantis)	43	51
0	9	Freedom	Freedom	NNP	compound	11	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP Freedom)	52	59
0	10	Team	Team	NNP	compound	11	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP Team)	60	64
0	11	Club	Club	NNP	obj	6	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP Club)	65	69
0	12	"	"	''	punct	11	O	 ('' "))	69	70
0	13	Always	always	RB	advmod	6	O	 (ADVP (RB Always))	72	78
0	14	great	great	JJ	xcomp	6	O	 (S (ADJP (JJ great)	79	84
0	15	to	to	TO	mark	16	O	 (S (VP (TO to)	85	87
0	16	see	see	VB	xcomp	14	O	 (VP (VB see)	88	91
0	17	another	another	DT	det	18	O	 (NP (DT another)	92	99
0	18	politician	politician	NN	obj	16	TITLE	 (NN politician))	100	110
0	19	grifting	grift	VBG	xcomp	16	O	 (S (VP (VBG grifting)	111	119
0	20	their	they	PRP$	nmod:poss	22	O	 (NP (PRP$ their)	120	125
0	21	uneducated	uneducated	JJ	amod	22	O	 (JJ uneducated)	126	136
0	22	fans	fan	NNS	obj	19	O	 (NNS fans))))))))))	137	141
0	23	.	.	.	punct	6	O	 (. .)))	141	142

