0	1	Discussion	discussion	NN	compound	2	O	 (ROOT (FRAG (NP (NN Discussion)	0	10
0	2	Thread	thread	NN	root	0	O	 (NN Thread))	11	17
0	3	:	:	:	punct	2	O	 (: :)	17	18
0	4	President	President	NNP	compound	5	TITLE	 (S (NP (NNP President)	19	28
0	5	Biden	Biden	NNP	nsubj	6	PERSON	 (NNP Biden))	29	34
0	6	provides	provide	VBZ	parataxis	2	O	 (VP (VBZ provides)	35	43
0	7	an	a	DT	det	8	O	 (NP (NP (DT an)	44	46
0	8	update	update	NN	obj	6	O	 (NN update))	47	53
0	9	on	on	IN	case	14	O	 (PP (IN on)	54	56
0	10	the	the	DT	det	14	O	 (NP (DT the)	57	60
0	11	Ukraine	Ukraine	NNP	compound	14	LOCATION	 (NNP Ukraine)	61	68
0	12	-	-	HYPH	punct	14	LOCATION	 (HYPH -)	68	69
0	13	Russia	Russia	NNP	compound	14	LOCATION	 (NNP Russia)	69	75
0	14	situation	situation	NN	nmod	8	O	 (NN situation))))))	76	85
0	15	.	.	.	punct	2	O	 (. .)))	85	86

1	1	1:00	1:00	CD	nummod	2	TIME	 (ROOT (FRAG (NP (CD 1:00)	87	91
1	2	p.m.	p.m.	NN	root	0	TIME	 (NN p.m.))	92	96
1	3	EST.	EST.	NNP	dep	2	TIME	 (NP (NNP EST.))	97	100
1	4	.	.	.	punct	2	O	 (. .)))	100	101

2	1	Lol	lol	UH	discourse	6	O	 (ROOT (S (INTJ (UH Lol))	103	106
2	2	Biden	Biden	NNP	nsubj	6	PERSON	 (NP (NNP Biden))	107	112
2	3	is	be	VBZ	cop	6	O	 (VP (VBZ is)	113	115
2	4	such	such	JJ	case	6	O	 (PP (JJ such)	116	120
2	5	a	a	DT	det	6	O	 (NP (DT a)	121	122
2	6	failure	failure	NN	root	0	O	 (NN failure))))))	123	130

