0	1	GOP	GOP	NNP	compound	2	ORGANIZATION	 (ROOT (S (S (NP (NNP GOP)	0	3
0	2	States	States	NNP	nsubj	4	O	 (NNP States))	4	10
0	3	Are	be	VBP	aux	4	O	 (VP (VBP Are)	11	14
0	4	Shredding	shred	VBG	root	0	O	 (VP (VBG Shredding)	15	24
0	5	Voting	Voting	NNP	compound	6	O	 (NP (NML (NML (NNP Voting)	25	31
0	6	Rights	Rights	NNPS	compound	9	O	 (NNPS Rights))	32	38
0	7	and	and	CC	cc	8	O	 (CC and)	39	42
0	8	Joe	Joe	NNP	conj	6	PERSON	 (NML (NNP Joe)))	43	46
0	9	Manchin	Manchin	NNP	obj	4	PERSON	 (NNP Manchin)))))	47	54
0	10	and	and	CC	cc	18	O	 (CC and)	55	58
0	11	Kyrsten	Kyrsten	NNP	compound	12	PERSON	 (S (NP (NNP Kyrsten)	59	66
0	12	Sinema	Sinema	NNP	nsubj	18	PERSON	 (NNP Sinema))	67	73
0	13	Are	be	VBP	cop	18	O	 (VP (VBP Are)	74	77
0	14	Now	now	RB	advmod	18	DATE	 (ADVP (RB Now))	78	81
0	15	Complicit	Complicit	NNP	compound	17	O	 (NP (NP (NML (NNP Complicit)	82	91
0	16	-	-	HYPH	punct	17	O	 (HYPH -)	92	93
0	17	Voter	Voter	NNP	compound	18	O	 (NNP Voter))	94	99
0	18	suppression	suppression	NN	conj	4	O	 (NN suppression))	100	111
0	19	is	be	VBZ	aux	20	O	 (SBAR (S (VP (VBZ is)	112	114
0	20	skyrocketing	skyrocket	VBG	acl:relcl	18	O	 (VP (VBG skyrocketing))))))))	115	127
0	21	and	and	CC	cc	23	O	 (CC and)	128	131
0	22	they	they	PRP	nsubj	23	O	 (S (NP (PRP they))	132	136
0	23	blocked	block	VBD	conj	4	O	 (VP (VBD blocked)	137	144
0	24	an	a	DT	det	25	O	 (NP (DT an)	145	147
0	25	effort	effort	NN	obj	23	O	 (NN effort))	148	154
0	26	to	to	TO	mark	27	O	 (S (VP (TO to)	155	157
0	27	stop	stop	VB	advcl	23	O	 (VP (VB stop)	158	162
0	28	it	it	PRP	nsubj	29	O	 (S (NP (PRP it))	163	165
0	29	Fake	fake	JJ	xcomp	27	O	 (ADJP (JJ Fake)	167	171
0	30	and	and	CC	cc	31	O	 (CC and)	172	175
0	31	gay	gay	JJ	conj	29	O	 (JJ gay))))))))))	176	179

