0	1	A	a	DT	det	5	O	 (ROOT (S (NP (DT A)	0	1
0	2	BrooklynDad	BrooklynDad	NNP	compound	5	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP BrooklynDad)	2	13
0	3	Defiant	defiant	JJ	amod	5	ORGANIZATION	 (JJ Defiant)	14	21
0	4	L	l	NN	compound	5	ORGANIZATION	 (NN L)	22	23
0	5	Q	q	NN	nsubj	7	ORGANIZATION	 (NN Q))	25	26
0	6	has	have	VBZ	aux	7	O	 (VP (VBZ has)	27	30
0	7	confirmed	confirm	VBN	root	0	O	 (VP (VBN confirmed)	31	40
0	8	that	that	IN	mark	12	O	 (SBAR (IN that)	41	45
0	9	Trump	Trump	NNP	nsubj	12	PERSON	 (S (NP (NNP Trump)	46	51
0	10	and	and	CC	cc	11	O	 (CC and)	52	55
0	11	Putin	Putin	NNP	conj	9	PERSON	 (NNP Putin))	56	61
0	12	spit	spit	VBD	ccomp	7	O	 (VP (VBD spit)	62	66
0	13	on	on	IN	case	15	O	 (PP (IN on)	67	69
0	14	each	each	DT	det	15	O	 (NP (DT each)	70	74
0	15	other	other	JJ	obl	12	O	 (JJ other)))	75	80
0	16	during	during	IN	case	17	O	 (PP (IN during)	81	87
0	17	sex	sex	NN	obl	12	O	 (NP (NN sex))))))))	88	91
0	18	.	.	.	punct	7	O	 (. .)))	91	92

1	1	Stay	stay	VB	root	0	O	 (ROOT (S (VP (VB Stay)	93	97
1	2	safe	safe	JJ	amod	3	O	 (NP (JJ safe)	98	102
1	3	comrades	comrade	NNS	obj	1	O	 (NNS comrades)))))	103	111

