0	1	CMV	cmv	NN	root	0	O	 (ROOT (FRAG (NP (NN CMV))	0	3
0	2	:	:	:	punct	1	O	 (: :)	3	4
0	3	Tucker	Tucker	NNP	compound	4	PERSON	 (NP (NP (NNP Tucker)	5	11
0	4	Carlson	Carlson	NNP	dep	1	PERSON	 (NNP Carlson))	12	19
0	5	asking	ask	VBG	acl	4	O	 (VP (VBG asking)	20	26
0	6	for	for	IN	mark	12	O	 (SBAR (IN for)	27	30
0	7	KBJ	KBJ	NNP	nmod:poss	10	ORGANIZATION	 (S (NP (NP (NNP KBJ)	31	34
0	8	's	's	POS	case	7	O	 (POS 's))	34	36
0	9	LSAT	lsat	NN	compound	10	O	 (NN LSAT)	37	41
0	10	score	score	NN	nsubj	12	O	 (NN score))	42	47
0	11	is	be	VBZ	cop	12	O	 (VP (VBZ is)	48	50
0	12	racist	racist	JJ	advcl	5	O	 (ADJP (JJ racist)	51	57
0	13	I	I	PRP	nsubj	15	O	 (SBAR (S (NP (PRP I))	59	60
0	14	'll	will	MD	aux	15	O	 (VP (MD 'll)	60	63
0	15	make	make	VB	ccomp	12	O	 (VP (VB make)	64	68
0	16	the	the	DT	det	17	O	 (NP (NP (DT the)	69	72
0	17	claim	claim	NN	obj	15	O	 (NN claim))	73	78
0	18	for	for	IN	case	19	O	 (PP (IN for)	79	82
0	19	you	you	PRP	nmod	17	O	 (NP (PRP you))))))))))))))	83	86
0	20	.	.	.	punct	1	O	 (. .)))	86	87

1	1	Tucker	Tucker	NNP	compound	2	PERSON	 (ROOT (S (NP (NNP Tucker)	89	95
1	2	Carlson	Carlson	NNP	nsubj	6	PERSON	 (NNP Carlson))	96	103
1	3	is	be	VBZ	cop	6	O	 (VP (VBZ is)	104	106
1	4	a	a	DT	det	6	O	 (NP (NP (DT a)	107	108
1	5	racist	racist	JJ	amod	6	O	 (JJ racist)	109	115
1	6	propagandist	propagandist	NN	root	0	O	 (NN propagandist))	116	128
1	7	with	with	IN	case	8	O	 (PP (IN with)	129	133
1	8	nothing	nothing	NN	nmod	6	O	 (NP (NP (NN nothing))	134	141
1	9	of	of	IN	case	10	O	 (PP (IN of)	142	144
1	10	value	value	NN	nmod	8	O	 (NP (NN value)	145	150
1	11	to	to	TO	mark	12	O	 (S (VP (TO to)	151	153
1	12	offer	offer	VB	acl	10	O	 (VP (VB offer)	154	159
1	13	society	society	NN	obj	12	O	 (NP (NN society)))))))))))	160	167
1	14	.	.	.	punct	6	O	 (. .)))	167	168

