0	1	Courtney	Courtney	NNP	compound	2	PERSON	 (ROOT (S (S (NP (NNP Courtney)	0	8
0	2	Love	Love	NNP	nsubj	6	PERSON	 (NNP Love))	9	13
0	3	was	be	VBD	cop	6	O	 (VP (VBD was)	14	17
0	4	on	on	IN	case	6	O	 (PP (IN on)	18	20
0	5	Epstein	Epstein	NNP	compound	6	LOCATION	 (NP (NNP Epstein)	21	28
0	6	Island	Island	NNP	root	0	LOCATION	 (NNP Island)))))	29	35
0	7	and	and	CC	cc	13	O	 (CC and)	36	39
0	8	she	she	PRP	nsubj	13	O	 (S (NP (PRP she))	40	43
0	9	was	be	VBD	cop	13	O	 (VP (VBD was)	44	47
0	10	in	in	IN	case	13	O	 (PP (IN in)	48	50
0	11	the	the	DT	det	13	O	 (NP (DT the)	51	54
0	12	FRAZZLED.rip	FRAZZLED.rip	NNP	compound	13	O	 (NNP FRAZZLED.rip)	55	67
0	13	video	video	NN	conj	6	O	 (NN video)))))	68	73
0	14	.	.	.	punct	6	O	 (. .)))	73	74

1	1	Kurt	Kurt	NNP	compound	3	PERSON	 (ROOT (S (NP (NNP Kurt)	75	79
1	2	Covains	Covains	NNP	compound	3	PERSON	 (NNP Covains)	80	87
1	3	Ex	Ex	NNP	nsubj	5	O	 (NNP Ex))	88	90
1	4	is	be	VBZ	cop	5	O	 (VP (VBZ is)	91	93
1	5	KEY	key	NN	root	0	O	 (NP (NP (NN KEY))	94	97
1	6	She	she	PRP	nsubj	9	O	 (SBAR (S (NP (PRP She))	99	102
1	7	’s	’s	VBZ	cop	9	O	 (VP (VBZ ’s)	102	104
1	8	a	a	DT	det	9	O	 (NP (DT a)	105	106
1	9	witch	witch	NN	acl:relcl	5	O	 (NN witch)))))))	107	112
1	10	.	.	.	punct	5	O	 (. .)))	112	113

2	1	Sacrificing	sacrifice	VBG	root	0	O	 (ROOT (S (VP (VBG Sacrificing)	114	125
2	2	children	child	NNS	obj	1	O	 (NP (NNS children)))	126	134
2	3	.	.	.	punct	1	O	 (. .)))	134	135

3	1	Kurt	Kurt	NNP	nsubj	2	PERSON	 (ROOT (S (NP (NNP Kurt))	136	140
3	2	said	say	VBD	root	0	O	 (VP (VBD said)	141	145
3	3	no	no	DT	obj	2	O	 (NP (DT no)	146	148
3	4	…	…	:	punct	3	O	 (: …)))	148	149
3	5	.	.	.	punct	2	O	 (. .)))	149	150

4	1	.	.	.	root	0	O	 (ROOT (. .))	150	151

5	1	the	the	DT	det	2	O	 (ROOT (S (NP (DT the)	151	154
5	2	rest	rest	NN	nsubj	4	O	 (NN rest))	155	159
5	3	is	be	VBZ	cop	4	O	 (VP (VBZ is)	160	162
5	4	history	history	NN	root	0	O	 (NP (NN history)))))	163	170

