0	1	Biden	Biden	NNP	nsubj	2	PERSON	 (ROOT (SQ (S (NP (NNP Biden))	0	5
0	2	reaffirms	reaffirm	VBZ	dep	16	O	 (VP (VBZ reaffirms)	6	15
0	3	pledge	pledge	NN	obj	2	O	 (NP (NN pledge))	16	22
0	4	to	to	TO	mark	5	O	 (S (VP (TO to)	23	25
0	5	nominate	nominate	VB	advcl	2	O	 (VP (VB nominate)	26	34
0	6	Black	black	JJ	amod	7	O	 (NP (JJ Black)	35	40
0	7	woman	woman	NN	obj	5	O	 (NN woman))	41	46
0	8	to	to	IN	case	10	O	 (PP (IN to)	47	49
0	9	Supreme	Supreme	NNP	compound	10	ORGANIZATION	 (NP (NNP Supreme)	50	57
0	10	Court	Court	NNP	obl	5	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP Court))))))))	58	63
0	11	Would	would	MD	aux	16	O	 (SQ (MD Would)	65	70
0	12	Kamala	Kamala	NNP	compound	13	PERSON	 (NP (NNP Kamala)	71	77
0	13	Harris	Harris	NNP	nsubj	16	PERSON	 (NNP Harris))	78	84
0	14	be	be	VB	cop	16	O	 (VP (VB be)	85	87
0	15	black	black	JJ	advmod	16	O	 (ADJP (JJ black)	88	93
0	16	enough	enough	JJ	root	0	O	 (JJ enough))))	94	100
0	17	?	?	.	punct	16	O	 (. ?)))	100	101

