0	1	Disney	Disney	NNP	compound	4	ORGANIZATION	 (ROOT (SINV (S (NP (NNP Disney)	0	6
0	2	CEO	CEO	NNP	compound	4	TITLE	 (NNP CEO)	7	10
0	3	Bob	Bob	NNP	compound	4	PERSON	 (NNP Bob)	11	14
0	4	Chapek	Chapek	NNP	nsubj	5	PERSON	 (NNP Chapek))	15	21
0	5	Apologizes	apologize	VBZ	ccomp	10	O	 (VP (VBZ Apologizes)	22	32
0	6	to	to	IN	case	8	O	 (PP (IN to)	33	35
0	7	LGBTQ	LGBTQ	NNP	compound	8	O	 (NP (NNP LGBTQ)	36	41
0	8	Employees	Employees	NNPS	obl	5	O	 (NNPS Employees)))))	42	51
0	9	,	,	,	punct	10	O	 (, ,)	51	52
0	10	Announces	announce	VBZ	root	0	O	 (VP (VBZ Announces)	53	62
0	11	Pause	pause	NN	obj	10	O	 (NP (NN Pause))	63	68
0	12	for	for	IN	case	14	O	 (PP (IN for)	69	72
0	13	Political	political	JJ	amod	14	O	 (NP (NP (JJ Political)	73	82
0	14	Donations	donation	NNS	obl	10	O	 (NNS Donations))	83	92
0	15	in	in	IN	case	16	O	 (PP (IN in)	93	95
0	16	Florida	Florida	NNP	nmod	14	STATE_OR_PROVINCE	 (NP (NNP Florida))))))	96	103
0	17	This	this	DT	nsubj	10	O	 (NP (NP (DT This))	105	109
0	18	just	just	RB	advmod	19	O	 (RRC (ADVP (RB just))	110	114
0	19	end	end	NN	acl:relcl	17	O	 (NP (NN end))))	115	118
0	20	!	!	.	punct	10	O	 (. !)))	118	119

1	1	Bob	Bob	NNP	compound	2	PERSON	 (ROOT (S (NP (NNP Bob)	120	123
1	2	Chapek	Chapek	NNP	nsubj:pass	5	PERSON	 (NNP Chapek))	124	130
1	3	will	will	MD	aux	5	O	 (VP (MD will)	131	135
1	4	be	be	VB	aux:pass	5	O	 (VP (VB be)	136	138
1	5	fired	fire	VBN	root	0	O	 (VP (VBN fired)	139	144
1	6	because	because	IN	mark	8	O	 (SBAR (IN because)	145	152
1	7	he	he	PRP	nsubj	8	O	 (S (NP (PRP he))	153	155
1	8	forgot	forget	VBD	advcl	5	O	 (VP (VBD forgot)	156	162
1	9	Disney	Disney	NNP	nsubj	12	ORGANIZATION	 (SBAR (S (NP (NNP Disney))	163	169
1	10	was	be	VBD	cop	12	O	 (VP (VBD was)	170	173
1	11	a	a	DT	det	12	O	 (NP (NP (DT a)	174	175
1	12	company	company	NN	ccomp	8	O	 (NN company))	176	183
1	13	for	for	IN	case	14	O	 (PP (IN for)	184	187
1	14	children	child	NNS	nmod	12	O	 (NP (NP (NNS children))	188	196
1	15	not	not	RB	advmod	16	O	 (NP (RB not)	197	200
1	16	pedophiles	pedophile	NNS	dep	14	O	 (NNS pedophiles))))))))))))))	201	211
1	17	.	.	.	punct	5	O	 (. .)))	211	212

