0	1	Trump	Trump	NNP	nsubj	2	PERSON	 (ROOT (S (NP (NNP Trump))	1	6
0	2	slams	slam	VBZ	root	0	O	 (VP (VBZ slams)	7	12
0	3	former	former	JJ	amod	4	O	 (SBAR (S (NP (NML (JJ former)	13	19
0	4	AG	AG	NNP	compound	6	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP AG))	20	22
0	5	Bill	Bill	NNP	compound	6	PERSON	 (NNP Bill)	23	27
0	6	Barr	Barr	NNP	nsubj	8	PERSON	 (NNP Barr))	28	32
0	7	,	,	,	punct	8	O	 (, ,)	32	33
0	8	calls	call	VBZ	ccomp	2	O	 (VP (VBZ calls)	34	39
0	9	Jan	Jan	NNP	obl:tmod	8	DATE	 (NP-TMP (NNP Jan)	40	43
0	10	6	6	CD	nummod	9	DATE	 (CD 6))	44	45
0	11	committee	committee	NN	nsubj	18	O	 (SBAR (S (NP (NP (NN committee))	46	55
0	12	a	a	DT	det	15	O	 (NP (DT a)	56	57
0	13	'	'	``	punct	15	O	 (`` ')	58	59
0	14	witch	witch	NN	compound	15	O	 (NN witch)	59	64
0	15	hunt	hunt	NN	dep	11	O	 (NN hunt)	65	69
0	16	,	,	,	punct	15	O	 (, ,)	69	70
0	17	'	'	''	punct	15	O	 ('' ')))	70	71
0	18	claims	claim	VBZ	ccomp	8	O	 (VP (VBZ claims)	72	78
0	19	Antifa	Antifa	NNP	compound	21	PERSON	 (NP (NP (NNP Antifa)	79	85
0	20	,	,	,	punct	21	O	 (, ,)	85	86
0	21	BLM	BLM	NNP	obj	18	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP BLM)	87	90
0	22	'	'	''	punct	21	O	 ('' '))	91	92
0	23	got	get	VBD	acl:relcl	21	O	 (SBAR (S (VP (VBD got)	92	95
0	24	away	away	RB	advmod	23	O	 (ADVP (RB away))	96	100
0	25	with	with	IN	case	26	O	 (PP (IN with)	101	105
0	26	murder	murder	NN	obl	23	CRIMINAL_CHARGE	 (NP (NN murder)	106	112
0	27	'	'	''	punct	26	O	 ('' ')))	112	113
0	28	Oh	oh	UH	dep	23	O	 (PRN (INTJ (UH Oh))	115	117
0	29	shit	shit	UH	discourse	28	O	 (INTJ (UH shit))))))))))))))	118	122
0	30	!	!	.	punct	2	O	 (. !)))	122	123

1	1	They	they	PRP	nsubj	2	O	 (ROOT (S (NP (PRP They))	124	128
1	2	caught	catch	VBD	root	0	O	 (VP (VBD caught)	129	135
1	3	another	another	DT	det	4	O	 (NP (DT another)	136	143
1	4	witch	witch	NN	obj	2	O	 (NN witch)))	144	149
1	5	!	!	.	punct	2	O	 (. !)))	149	150

2	1	https://www.thedailybeast.com/proud-boys-leader-enrique-tarrio-charged-with-conspiracy-for-jan-6-capitol-riot	https://www.thedailybeast.com/proud-boys-leader-enrique-tarrio-charged-with-conspiracy-for-jan-6-capitol-riot	ADD	root	0	URL	 (ROOT (NP (ADD https://www.thedailybeast.com/proud-boys-leader-enrique-tarrio-charged-with-conspiracy-for-jan-6-capitol-riot)))	151	260

