0	1	Marjorie	Marjorie	NNP	compound	3	PERSON	 (ROOT (S (NP (NP (NNP Marjorie)	0	8
0	2	Taylor	Taylor	NNP	compound	3	PERSON	 (NNP Taylor)	9	15
0	3	Greene	Greene	NNP	nmod:poss	7	PERSON	 (NNP Greene)	16	22
0	4	’s	’s	POS	case	3	O	 (POS ’s))	22	24
0	5	personal	personal	JJ	amod	7	O	 (JJ personal)	25	33
0	6	Twitter	Twitter	NNP	compound	7	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP Twitter)	34	41
0	7	account	account	NN	nsubj	22	O	 (NN account))	42	49
0	8	permanently	permanently	RB	advmod	9	O	 (S (ADVP (RB permanently))	50	61
0	9	banned	ban	VBN	dep	22	O	 (VP (VBN banned)	62	68
0	10	over	over	IN	case	19	O	 (PP (IN over)	69	73
0	11	‘	‘	``	punct	19	O	 (`` ‘)	74	75
0	12	repeated	repeat	VBN	amod	13	O	 (NP (NP (VBN repeated)	75	83
0	13	violations	violation	NNS	nmod:poss	19	O	 (NNS violations)	84	94
0	14	’	’	POS	case	13	O	 (POS ’))	94	95
0	15	of	of	IN	case	16	O	 (NML (PP (IN of)	96	98
0	16	COVID	COVID	NNP	nmod	19	O	 (NP (NNP COVID)))	99	104
0	17	-	-	HYPH	punct	19	O	 (HYPH -)	104	105
0	18	19	19	CD	nummod	19	O	 (NP (CD 19)	105	107
0	19	misinformation	misinformation	NN	obl	9	O	 (NN misinformation)))))))	108	122
0	20	policy	policy	NN	compound	21	O	 (NP (NN policy)	123	129
0	21	Twitter	Twitter	NNP	nsubj	22	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP Twitter))	131	138
0	22	allows	allow	VBZ	root	0	O	 (VP (VBZ allows)	139	145
0	23	pedophiles	pedophile	NNS	obj	22	O	 (NP (NP (NNS pedophiles))	146	156
0	24	but	but	CC	case	26	O	 (PP (CC but)	157	160
0	25	bans	ban	NNS	compound	26	O	 (NP (NNS bans)	161	165
0	26	conservatives	conservative	NNS	nmod	23	O	 (NNS conservatives)))))	166	179
0	27	.	.	.	punct	22	O	 (. .)))	179	180

1	1	No	no	DT	det	2	O	 (ROOT (NP (DT No)	181	183
1	2	surprise	surprise	NN	root	0	O	 (NN surprise)	184	192
1	3	.	.	.	punct	2	O	 (. .)))	192	193

2	1	Twitter	Twitter	NNP	nsubj	2	O	 (ROOT (S (NP (NNP Twitter))	194	201
2	2	sucks	suck	VBZ	root	0	O	 (VP (VBZ sucks)	202	207
2	3	ass	ass	NN	obj	2	O	 (NP (NN ass)))	208	211
2	4	.	.	.	punct	2	O	 (. .)))	211	212

