0	1	Man	Man	NNP	nsubj	14	O	 (ROOT (S (NP (NP (NNP Man))	0	3
0	2	Who	who	WP	nsubj	3	O	 (SBAR (WHNP (WP Who))	4	7
0	3	Rammed	ram	VBD	acl:relcl	1	O	 (S (VP (VBD Rammed)	8	14
0	4	Car	car	NN	obj	3	O	 (NP (NN Car))	15	18
0	5	into	into	IN	case	8	O	 (PP (IN into)	19	23
0	6	Winnipeg	Winnipeg	NNP	compound	8	ORGANIZATION	 (NP (NP (NNP Winnipeg)	24	32
0	7	Freedom	Freedom	NNP	compound	8	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP Freedom)	33	40
0	8	Convoy	Convoy	NNP	obl	3	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP Convoy))	41	47
0	9	Protesters	protester	NNS	dep	8	ORGANIZATION	 (NP (NNS Protesters))))))))	48	58
0	10	is	be	VBZ	cop	14	O	 (VP (VBZ is)	59	61
0	11	Antifa	Antifa	NNP	compound	14	O	 (NP (NP (NNP Antifa)	62	68
0	12	Activist	Activist	NNP	compound	14	TITLE	 (NNP Activist)	69	77
0	13	David	David	NNP	compound	14	PERSON	 (NNP David)	78	83
0	14	Zegarac	Zegarac	NNP	root	0	PERSON	 (NNP Zegarac))	84	91
0	15	I	I	PRP	nsubj	17	O	 (SBAR (S (NP (PRP I))	93	94
0	16	’m	’m	VBP	cop	17	O	 (VP (VBP ’m)	94	96
0	17	ready	ready	JJ	acl:relcl	14	O	 (ADJP (JJ ready)	97	102
0	18	to	to	TO	mark	19	O	 (S (VP (TO to)	103	105
0	19	see	see	VB	xcomp	17	O	 (VP (VB see)	106	109
0	20	the	the	DT	det	21	O	 (S (NP (DT the)	110	113
0	21	fucktard	fucktard	NN	nsubj	22	O	 (NN fucktard))	114	122
0	22	get	get	VB	ccomp	19	O	 (VP (VP (VB get)	123	126
0	23	a	a	DT	det	24	O	 (NP (DT a)	127	128
0	24	slap	slap	NN	obj	22	O	 (NN slap))	129	133
0	25	on	on	IN	case	27	O	 (PP (IN on)	134	136
0	26	the	the	DT	det	27	O	 (NP (DT the)	137	140
0	27	wrist	wrist	NN	obl	22	O	 (NN wrist))))	141	146
0	28	and	and	CC	cc	30	O	 (CC and)	147	150
0	29	be	be	VB	aux:pass	30	O	 (VP (VB be)	151	153
0	30	released	release	VBN	conj	22	O	 (VP (VBN released))))))))))))))	154	162
0	31	.	.	.	punct	14	O	 (. .)))	162	163

