0	1	Peter	Peter	NNP	compound	2	PERSON	 (ROOT (S (NP (NNP Peter)	0	5
0	2	Doocy	Doocy	NNP	nsubj	3	PERSON	 (NNP Doocy))	6	11
0	3	Asks	ask	VBZ	root	0	O	 (VP (VBZ Asks)	12	16
0	4	For	for	IN	case	7	O	 (SBAR (S (PP (IN For)	17	20
0	5	A	a	DT	det	7	O	 (NP (NP (DT A)	21	22
0	6	Straight	straight	RB	advmod	7	O	 (RB Straight)	23	31
0	7	Answer	answer	NN	obl	21	O	 (NN Answer))	32	38
0	8	On	on	IN	case	9	O	 (SBAR (S (PP (IN On)	39	41
0	9	Keystone	keystone	NN	obl	11	ORGANIZATION	 (NP (NN Keystone)))	42	50
0	10	,	,	,	punct	11	O	 (, ,)	50	51
0	11	Gets	get	VBZ	acl:relcl	7	O	 (VP (VBZ Gets)	52	56
0	12	The	the	DT	det	13	O	 (NP (DT The)	57	60
0	13	Runaround	runaround	NN	obj	11	O	 (NN Runaround))	61	70
0	14	From	from	IN	case	16	O	 (PP (IN From)	71	75
0	15	Jen	Jen	NNP	compound	16	PERSON	 (NP (NNP Jen)	76	79
0	16	Psaki	Psaki	NNP	obl	11	PERSON	 (NNP Psaki))))))))	80	85
0	17	She	she	PRP	nsubj	21	O	 (NP (PRP She))	87	90
0	18	's	be	VBZ	cop	21	O	 (VP (VBZ 's)	90	92
0	19	such	such	PDT	det:predet	21	O	 (NP (NP (NP (PDT such)	93	97
0	20	a	a	DT	det	21	O	 (DT a)	98	99
0	21	fucking	fucking	JJ	ccomp	3	O	 (JJ fucking))	100	107
0	22	useless	useless	JJ	advmod	23	O	 (ADJP (JJ useless)	108	115
0	23	degenerate	degenerate	JJ	amod	21	O	 (JJ degenerate)))	116	126
0	24	...	...	NFP	punct	21	O	 (NFP ...)	126	129
0	25	Ugly	Ugly	NNP	compound	26	O	 (NP (NP (NNP Ugly)	130	134
0	26	dog	dog	NN	dep	21	O	 (NN dog))	135	138
0	27	she	she	PRP	nsubj	28	O	 (SBAR (S (NP (PRP she))	139	142
0	28	is	be	VBZ	acl:relcl	26	O	 (VP (VBZ is))))))))))))	143	145

