0	1	Ron	Ron	NNP	compound	2	PERSON	 (ROOT (S (NP (NP (NNP Ron)	0	3
0	2	Paul	Paul	NNP	nsubj	21	PERSON	 (NNP Paul))	4	8
0	3	,	,	,	punct	2	O	 (, ,)	8	9
0	4	Congressman	Congressman	NNP	appos	2	TITLE	 (NP (NP (NP (NNP Congressman))	10	21
0	5	of	of	IN	case	7	O	 (PP (IN of)	22	24
0	6	30	30	CD	nummod	7	DURATION	 (NP (CD 30)	25	27
0	7	Years	year	NNS	nmod	4	DURATION	 (NNS Years))))	28	33
0	8	,	,	,	punct	4	O	 (, ,)	33	34
0	9	Banned	ban	VBN	acl	4	O	 (VP (VBN Banned)	35	41
0	10	on	on	IN	case	11	O	 (PP (IN on)	42	44
0	11	Facebook	Facebook	NNP	obl	9	ORGANIZATION	 (NP (NNP Facebook))))))	45	53
0	12	After	after	IN	mark	13	O	 (PP (IN After)	54	59
0	13	Quoting	quote	VBG	advcl	21	O	 (S (VP (VBG Quoting)	60	67
0	14	Pfizer	Pfizer	NNP	compound	16	O	 (NP (NNP Pfizer)	68	74
0	15	CEO	CEO	NNP	compound	16	TITLE	 (NNP CEO)	75	78
0	16	Ok	Ok	NNP	obj	13	O	 (NNP Ok)))))	80	82
0	17	,	,	,	punct	21	O	 (, ,)	82	83
0	18	these	these	DT	det	19	O	 (NP (DT these)	84	89
0	19	bastards	bastard	NNS	nsubj	21	O	 (NNS bastards))	90	98
0	20	officially	officially	RB	advmod	21	O	 (ADVP (RB officially))	99	109
0	21	went	go	VBD	root	0	O	 (VP (VBD went)	110	114
0	22	too	too	RB	advmod	23	O	 (ADVP (RB too)	115	118
0	23	far	far	RB	advmod	21	O	 (RB far)))	119	122
0	24	.	.	.	punct	21	O	 (. .)))	122	123

1	1	No	no	DT	det	2	O	 (ROOT (S (NP (DT No)	124	126
1	2	one	one	NN	nsubj	3	NUMBER	 (NN one))	127	130
1	3	goes	go	VBZ	root	0	O	 (VP (VP (VBZ goes)	131	135
1	4	after	after	IN	case	6	O	 (PP (IN after)	136	141
1	5	Ron	Ron	NNP	compound	6	PERSON	 (NP (NNP Ron)	142	145
1	6	Paul	Paul	NNP	obl	3	PERSON	 (NNP Paul))))	146	150
1	7	and	and	CC	cc	8	O	 (CC and)	151	154
1	8	walks	walk	VBZ	conj	3	O	 (VP (VBZ walks)	155	160
1	9	away	away	RB	advmod	8	O	 (ADVP (RB away))	161	165
1	10	without	without	IN	case	12	O	 (PP (IN without)	166	173
1	11	a	a	DT	det	12	O	 (NP (DT a)	174	175
1	12	scratch	scratch	NN	obl	8	O	 (NN scratch)))))	176	183
1	13	!	!	.	punct	3	O	 (. !)))	183	184

