0	1	‘	‘	``	punct	5	O	 (ROOT (S (`` ‘)	0	1
0	2	If	if	IN	advcl	5	O	 (S (SBAR (IN If))	1	3
0	3	AOC	AOC	NNP	nsubj	5	ORGANIZATION	 (NP (NNP AOC))	4	7
0	4	Was	be	VBD	cop	5	O	 (VP (VBD Was)	8	11
0	5	Fat	Fat	NNP	root	0	O	 (NP (NNP Fat))))	12	15
0	6	And	and	CC	cc	13	O	 (CC And)	16	19
0	7	In	in	IN	case	9	O	 (SQ (PP (IN In)	20	22
0	8	Her	she	PRP$	nmod:poss	9	O	 (NP (PRP$ Her)	23	26
0	9	60s	60	NNS	obl	13	O	 (NNS 60s)))	27	30
0	10	,	,	,	punct	13	O	 (, ,)	30	31
0	11	Would	would	MD	aux	13	O	 (MD Would)	32	37
0	12	Anyone	anyone	NN	nsubj	13	O	 (NP (NN Anyone))	38	44
0	13	Listen	listen	VB	conj	5	O	 (VP (VB Listen)))	45	51
0	14	?	?	.	punct	5	O	 (. ?)	51	52
0	15	’	’	''	punct	5	O	 ('' ’)))	52	53

1	1	:	:	:	punct	8	O	 (ROOT (S (: :)	53	54
1	2	Adam	Adam	NNP	compound	3	PERSON	 (S (PP (NP (NP (NNP Adam)	55	59
1	3	Carolla	Carolla	NNP	nmod:poss	5	PERSON	 (NNP Carolla)	60	67
1	4	’s	’s	POS	case	3	O	 (POS ’s))	67	69
1	5	Observations	Observations	NNPS	obl	8	O	 (NNPS Observations))	70	82
1	6	On	on	IN	case	5	O	 (IN On))	83	85
1	7	Hannity	Hannity	NNP	nsubj	8	ORGANIZATION	 (NP (NNP Hannity))	86	93
1	8	Cause	cause	VB	root	0	ORGANIZATION	 (VP (VB Cause)	94	99
1	9	Twitter	Twitter	NNP	compound	10	ORGANIZATION	 (NP (NP (NNP Twitter)	100	107
1	10	Meltdown	Meltdown	NNP	obj	8	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP Meltdown))	108	116
1	11	I	I	PRP	nsubj	12	O	 (SBAR (S (NP (PRP I))	118	119
1	12	stopped	stop	VBD	acl:relcl	10	O	 (VP (VBD stopped)	120	127
1	13	listening	listen	VBG	xcomp	12	O	 (S (VP (VBG listening)	128	137
1	14	to	to	IN	case	15	O	 (PP (IN to)	138	140
1	15	her	she	PRP	obl	13	O	 (NP (PRP her)))))))))	141	144
1	16	when	when	WRB	advmod	19	O	 (SBAR (WHADVP (WRB when))	145	149
1	17	she	she	PRP	nsubj	19	O	 (S (NP (PRP she))	150	153
1	18	first	first	RB	advmod	19	ORDINAL	 (ADVP (RB first))	154	159
1	19	spoke	speak	VBD	advcl	8	O	 (VP (VBD spoke))))))	160	165
1	20	but	but	CC	cc	23	O	 (CC but)	166	169
1	21	those	those	DT	det	22	O	 (S (NP (DT those)	170	175
1	22	tits	tit	NNS	nsubj	23	O	 (NNS tits))	176	180
1	23	keep	keep	VBP	conj	8	O	 (VP (VBP keep)	181	185
1	24	me	I	PRP	nsubj	25	O	 (S (NP (PRP me))	186	188
1	25	entertained	entertained	JJ	xcomp	23	O	 (ADJP (JJ entertained)))))	189	200
1	26	.	.	.	punct	8	O	 (. .)))	200	201

