0	1	While	while	IN	mark	5	O	 (ROOT (S (SBAR (IN While)	0	5
0	2	r	r	NN	compound	4	O	 (S (NP (NN r)	6	7
0	3	/	/	HYPH	punct	4	O	 (HYPH /)	7	8
0	4	Conspiracy	conspiracy	NN	nsubj	5	ORGANIZATION	 (NN Conspiracy))	8	18
0	5	Kicks	kick	VBZ	advcl	13	ORGANIZATION	 (VP (VBZ Kicks)	19	24
0	6	Rocks	Rocks	NNP	obj	5	ORGANIZATION	 (NP (NNP Rocks)))))	25	30
0	7	-	-	:	punct	13	O	 (: -)	31	32
0	8	I	I	PRP	nsubj	13	O	 (NP (PRP I))	33	34
0	9	'm	be	VBP	cop	13	O	 (VP (VBP 'm)	34	36
0	10	in	in	IN	case	13	O	 (PP (IN in)	37	39
0	11	the	the	DT	det	13	O	 (NP (DT the)	40	43
0	12	Space	Space	NNP	compound	13	O	 (NML (NNP Space)	44	49
0	13	Force	Force	NNP	root	0	O	 (NNP Force)))))	50	55
0	14	!	!	.	punct	13	O	 (. !)))	55	56

1	1	How	how	WRB	dep	2	O	 (ROOT (FRAG (WHADVP (WRB How))	57	60
1	2	Crazy	Crazy	NNP	root	0	O	 (NP (NNP Crazy))	61	66
1	3	!?!?!?!?	!?!?!?!?	NFP	punct	2	O	 (NFP !?!?!?!?)))	66	74

2	1	JFK	JFK	NNP	compound	2	PERSON	 (ROOT (NP (NNP JFK)	76	79
2	2	Jr.	Jr.	NNP	root	0	PERSON	 (NNP Jr.)	80	82
2	3	.	.	.	punct	2	O	 (. .)))	82	83

3	1	Is	be	VBZ	root	0	O	 (ROOT (S (VP (VBZ Is)	84	86
3	2	back	back	RB	advmod	1	O	 (ADVP (RB back)))	87	91
3	3	.	.	.	punct	1	O	 (. .)))	91	92

4	1	Run	Run	NNP	root	0	O	 (ROOT (FRAG (NP (NNP Run))	94	97
4	2	,	,	,	punct	1	O	 (, ,)	97	98
4	3	Nazi	Nazi	NNP	compound	4	IDEOLOGY	 (NP (NNP Nazi)	99	103
4	4	Scum	Scum	NNP	appos	1	MISC	 (NNP Scum))	104	108
4	5	.	.	.	punct	1	O	 (. .)))	108	109

5	1	(	(	-LRB-	punct	3	O	 (ROOT (PRN (-LRB- -LRB-) (S (NP (DT That)) (VP (VBZ rhymes) (INTJ (UH lol)))) (-RRB- -RRB-)))	111	112
5	2	That	that	DT	nsubj	3	O		112	116
5	3	rhymes	rhyme	VBZ	root	0	O		117	123
5	4	lol	lol	UH	discourse	3	O		124	127
5	5	)	)	-RRB-	punct	3	O		127	128

