0	1	I	I	PRP	nsubj	5	O	 (ROOT (S (NP (PRP I))	0	1
0	2	am	be	VBP	cop	5	O	 (VP (VP (VBP am)	2	4
0	3	in	in	IN	case	5	O	 (PP (IN in)	5	7
0	4	the	the	DT	det	5	O	 (NP (DT the)	8	11
0	5	USA	USA	NNP	root	0	COUNTRY	 (NNP USA))))	12	15
0	6	and	and	CC	cc	8	O	 (CC and)	16	19
0	7	am	be	VBP	cop	8	O	 (VP (VBP am)	20	22
0	8	unable	unable	JJ	conj	5	O	 (ADJP (JJ unable))	23	29
0	9	to	to	TO	mark	10	O	 (S (VP (TO to)	30	32
0	10	reach	reach	VB	xcomp	8	O	 (VP (VB reach)	33	38
0	11	RT	rt	NN	obj	10	O	 (NP (NN RT)))))	39	41
0	12	(	(	-LRB-	punct	14	O	 (PRN (-LRB- -LRB-) (NP (NNP Russia) (NNP Today)) (-RRB- -RRB-)))) (. .)))	42	43
0	13	Russia	Russia	NNP	compound	14	COUNTRY		43	49
0	14	Today	Today	NNP	dep	8	DATE		50	55
0	15	)	)	-RRB-	punct	14	O		55	56
0	16	.	.	.	punct	5	O		56	57

1	1	I	I	PRP	nsubj	5	O	 (ROOT (S (NP (PRP I))	58	59
1	2	also	also	RB	advmod	5	O	 (ADVP (RB also))	60	64
1	3	can	can	MD	aux	5	O	 (VP (MD can)	65	68
1	4	not	not	RB	advmod	5	O	 (RB not)	68	71
1	5	reach	reach	VB	root	0	O	 (VP (VB reach)	72	77
1	6	any	any	DT	det	7	O	 (NP (NP (DT any)	78	81
1	7	websites	website	NNS	obj	5	O	 (NNS websites))	82	90
1	8	of	of	IN	case	11	O	 (PP (IN of)	91	93
1	9	the	the	DT	det	11	O	 (NP (DT the)	94	97
1	10	Russian	russian	JJ	amod	11	NATIONALITY	 (JJ Russian)	98	105
1	11	Government	government	NN	nmod	7	O	 (NN Government))))))	106	116
1	12	.	.	.	punct	5	O	 (. .)))	116	117

2	1	The	the	DT	det	2	O	 (ROOT (S (NP (DT The)	118	121
2	2	Internet	internet	NN	nsubj:pass	5	MISC	 (NN Internet))	122	130
2	3	has	have	VBZ	aux	5	O	 (VP (VBZ has)	131	134
2	4	been	be	VBN	aux:pass	5	O	 (VP (VBN been)	135	139
2	5	weaponized	weaponize	VBN	root	0	O	 (VP (VBN weaponized)	140	150
2	6	against	against	IN	case	7	O	 (PP (IN against)	151	158
2	7	Russia	Russia	NNP	obl	5	COUNTRY	 (NP (NNP Russia))))))	159	165
2	8	.	.	.	punct	5	O	 (. .)))	165	166

3	1	I	I	PRP	nsubj	2	O	 (ROOT (S (S (NP (PRP I))	167	168
3	2	suspect	suspect	VBP	root	0	O	 (VP (VBP suspect)	169	176
3	3	the	the	DT	det	4	O	 (NP (NP (DT the)	177	180
3	4	people	people	NNS	obj	2	O	 (NNS people))	181	187
3	5	who	who	WP	nsubj	6	O	 (SBAR (WHNP (WP who))	188	191
3	6	control	control	VBP	acl:relcl	4	O	 (S (VP (VBP control)	192	199
3	7	the	the	DT	det	8	O	 (NP (NP (DT the)	200	203
3	8	Government	government	NN	obj	6	ORGANIZATION	 (NN Government))	204	214
3	9	of	of	IN	case	11	ORGANIZATION	 (PP (IN of)	215	217
3	10	the	the	DT	det	11	ORGANIZATION	 (NP (DT the)	218	221
3	11	USA	USA	NNP	nmod	8	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP USA))))))))))	222	225
3	12	and	and	CC	cc	19	O	 (CC and)	226	229
3	13	the	the	DT	det	16	O	 (S (NP (DT the)	230	233
3	14	USA	USA	NNP	compound	16	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP USA)	234	237
3	15	Deep	Deep	NNP	compound	16	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP Deep)	238	242
3	16	State	State	NNP	nsubj	19	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP State))	243	248
3	17	are	be	VBP	cop	19	O	 (VP (VBP are)	249	252
3	18	behind	behind	IN	case	19	O	 (PP (IN behind)	253	259
3	19	this	this	DT	conj	2	O	 (NP (DT this)))))	260	264
3	20	.	.	.	punct	2	O	 (. .)))	264	265

4	1	Boo	Boo	NNP	nsubj	3	O	 (ROOT (S (NP (NNP Boo))	267	270
4	2	fucking	fucking	RB	advmod	3	O	 (ADVP (RB fucking))	271	278
4	3	hoo	hoo	VBP	root	0	O	 (VP (VBP hoo)	279	282
4	4	you	you	PRP	nsubj	8	O	 (S (NP (PRP you))	283	286
4	5	whiney	whiney	JJ	amod	8	O	 (NP (JJ whiney)	287	293
4	6	little	little	JJ	amod	8	O	 (JJ little)	294	300
4	7	commie	commie	NN	compound	8	O	 (NN commie)	301	307
4	8	bitch	bitch	NN	xcomp	3	O	 (NN bitch))))	308	313
4	9	.	.	.	punct	3	O	 (. .)))	313	314

5	1	Beed	beed	VBN	root	0	LOCATION	 (ROOT (S (VP (VBN Beed)	315	319
5	2	over	over	IN	case	4	O	 (PP (IN over)	320	324
5	3	a	a	DT	det	4	O	 (NP (DT a)	325	326
5	4	take	take	VB	obl	1	O	 (NML (S (VP (VB take)	327	331
5	5	Vlad	Vlad	NNP	compound	7	PERSON	 (NP (NNP Vlad)	332	336
5	6	the	the	DT	det	7	O	 (DT the)	337	340
5	7	Invader	Invader	NNP	obj	4	O	 (NNP Invader))	341	348
5	8	like	like	IN	case	10	O	 (PP (IN like)	349	353
5	9	a	a	DT	det	10	O	 (NP (DT a)	354	355
5	10	man	man	NN	obl	4	O	 (NN man)))))))))	356	359
5	11	.	.	.	punct	1	O	 (. .)))	359	360

