0	1	ABC	ABC	NNP	nsubj	2	ORGANIZATION	 (ROOT (S (NP (NNP ABC))	0	3
0	2	slammed	slam	VBD	root	0	O	 (VP (VBD slammed)	4	11
0	3	for	for	IN	mark	4	O	 (PP (IN for)	12	15
0	4	suspending	suspend	VBG	advcl	2	O	 (S (VP (VP (VBG suspending)	16	26
0	5	Whoopi	Whoopi	NNP	compound	6	PERSON	 (NP (NP (NNP Whoopi)	27	33
0	6	Goldberg	Goldberg	NNP	obj	4	PERSON	 (NNP Goldberg))	34	42
0	7	for	for	IN	case	9	O	 (PP (IN for)	43	46
0	8	Holocaust	Holocaust	NNP	compound	9	O	 (NP (NNP Holocaust)	47	56
0	9	remark	remark	NN	nmod	6	O	 (NN remark)))))	57	63
0	10	but	but	CC	cc	11	O	 (CC but)	64	67
0	11	firing	fire	VBG	conj	4	O	 (VP (VBG firing)	68	74
0	12	Roseanne	Roseanne	NNP	obj	11	PERSON	 (NP (NP (NNP Roseanne))	75	83
0	13	for	for	IN	case	18	O	 (PP (IN for)	84	87
0	14	offensive	offensive	JJ	amod	18	O	 (NP (JJ offensive)	88	97
0	15	tweet	tweet	NN	compound	18	O	 (NN tweet)	98	103
0	16	Peak	peak	NN	compound	18	O	 (NN Peak)	105	109
0	17	clown	clown	NN	compound	18	TITLE	 (NN clown)	110	115
0	18	world	world	NN	nmod	12	O	 (NN world)))))))))	116	121
0	19	.	.	.	punct	2	O	 (. .)))	121	122

1	1	Lefties	lefty	NNS	nsubj	4	O	 (ROOT (S (S (NP (NNS Lefties))	123	130
1	2	are	be	VBP	cop	4	O	 (VP (VBP are)	131	134
1	3	so	so	RB	advmod	4	O	 (ADJP (RB so)	135	137
1	4	backward	backward	JJ	root	0	O	 (JJ backward)	138	146
1	5	Whoopie	whoopie	NN	nsubj	6	PERSON	 (SBAR (S (NP (NN Whoopie))	147	154
1	6	thinks	think	VBZ	ccomp	4	O	 (VP (VBZ thinks)	155	161
1	7	that	that	IN	mark	11	O	 (SBAR (IN that)	162	166
1	8	modern	modern	JJ	amod	9	O	 (S (NP (JJ modern)	167	173
1	9	republicans	republican	NNS	nsubj	11	O	 (NNS republicans))	174	185
1	10	are	be	VBP	cop	11	O	 (VP (VBP are)	186	189
1	11	racist	racist	JJ	ccomp	6	O	 (ADJP (JJ racist)))))))))))	190	196
1	12	but	but	CC	cc	17	O	 (CC but)	197	200
1	13	Hitler	Hitler	NNP	nsubj	17	PERSON	 (S (NP (NNP Hitler))	201	207
1	14	was	be	VBD	cop	17	O	 (VP (VBD was)	208	211
1	15	not	not	RB	advmod	17	O	 (RB not)	212	215
1	16	a	a	DT	det	17	O	 (NP (DT a)	216	217
1	17	racist	racist	NN	conj	4	O	 (NN racist))))	218	224
1	18	.	.	.	punct	4	O	 (. .)))	224	225

