0	1	Liberal	liberal	JJ	amod	4	ORGANIZATION	 (ROOT (S (PP (NP (JJ Liberal)	0	7
0	2	Media	Media	NNP	compound	3	ORGANIZATION	 (NML (NNP Media)	8	13
0	3	Excuses	Excuses	NNPS	compound	4	ORGANIZATION	 (NNPS Excuses))	14	21
0	4	Biden	Biden	NNP	obl	17	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP Biden))	22	27
0	5	For	for	IN	case	4	ORGANIZATION	 (IN For))	28	31
0	6	Assault	assault	NN	nsubj	17	ORGANIZATION	 (NP (NP (NN Assault))	32	39
0	7	on	on	IN	case	8	O	 (PP (IN on)	40	42
0	8	Reporter	reporter	NN	nmod	6	TITLE	 (NP (NP (NN Reporter))	43	51
0	9	That	that	IN	mark	13	O	 (SBAR (IN That)	52	56
0	10	Trump	Trump	NNP	nsubj	13	O	 (S (NP (NNP Trump))	57	62
0	11	Could	could	MD	aux	13	O	 (VP (MD Could)	63	68
0	12	Never	never	RB	advmod	13	O	 (ADVP (RB Never))	69	74
0	13	Get	get	VB	dep	8	O	 (VP (VB Get))))))))	75	78
0	14	Away	away	RB	advmod	17	O	 (ADVP (RB Away)	79	83
0	15	With	with	IN	case	16	O	 (PP (IN With)	84	88
0	16	Trump	Trump	NNP	obl	14	PERSON	 (NP (NNP Trump))))	90	95
0	17	got	get	VBD	root	0	O	 (VP (VBD got)	96	99
0	18	away	away	RB	advmod	17	O	 (ADVP (RB away))	100	104
0	19	with	with	IN	case	20	O	 (PP (IN with)	105	109
0	20	treason	treason	NN	obl	17	CRIMINAL_CHARGE	 (NP (NN treason))))	110	117
0	21	…	…	:	punct	17	O	 (: …)))	117	118

