0	1	Basement	basement	NN	root	0	O	 (ROOT (FRAG (NP (NN Basement))	0	8
0	2	Joe	Joe	NNP	nsubj	3	PERSON	 (S (NP (NNP Joe))	9	12
0	3	thinks	think	VBZ	dep	1	O	 (VP (VBZ thinks)	13	19
0	4	Cryptocurrencies	Cryptocurrencies	NNPS	nsubj	10	O	 (SBAR (S (NP (NNPS Cryptocurrencies))	20	36
0	5	are	be	VBP	cop	10	O	 (VP (VBP are)	37	40
0	6	a	a	DT	det	10	O	 (NP (DT a)	41	42
0	7	"	"	``	punct	10	O	 (`` ")	43	44
0	8	National	National	NNP	compound	9	O	 (NML (NNP National)	44	52
0	9	Security	Security	NNP	compound	10	O	 (NNP Security))	53	61
0	10	Threat	threat	NN	ccomp	3	O	 (NN Threat)	62	68
0	11	"	"	''	punct	10	O	 ('' ")))))))	68	69
0	12	---	---	,	punct	1	O	 (, ---)	70	73
0	13	So	so	RB	advmod	16	O	 (S (ADVP (RB So))	74	76
0	14	we	we	PRP	nsubj	16	O	 (NP (PRP we))	77	79
0	15	're	be	VBP	aux	16	O	 (VP (VBP 're)	79	82
0	16	doing	do	VBG	parataxis	1	O	 (VP (VBG doing)	83	88
0	17	crypto	crypto	NN	compound	19	O	 (NP (NN crypto)	89	95
0	18	-	-	HYPH	punct	19	O	 (HYPH -)	95	96
0	19	terrorists	terrorist	NNS	obj	16	O	 (NNS terrorists))	96	106
0	20	now	now	RB	advmod	16	DATE	 (ADVP (RB now))	107	110
0	21	,	,	,	punct	16	O	 (, ,)	110	111
0	22	hmmm	hmmm	UH	discourse	16	O	 (INTJ (UH hmmm)))))	112	116
0	23	?	?	.	punct	1	O	 (. ?)))	116	117

1	1	A	a	DT	det	2	O	 (ROOT (S (NP (NP (DT A)	119	120
1	2	threat	threat	NN	nsubj	11	O	 (NN threat))	121	127
1	3	to	to	IN	case	6	O	 (PP (IN to)	128	130
1	4	the	the	DT	det	6	O	 (NP (DT the)	131	134
1	5	Central	Central	NNP	compound	6	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP Central)	135	142
1	6	Bank	Bank	NNP	nmod	2	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP Bank))))	143	147
1	7	…	…	:	punct	11	O	 (: …)	147	148
1	8	it	it	PRP	nsubj	11	O	 (NP (PRP it))	149	151
1	9	’s	’s	VBZ	cop	11	O	 (VP (VBZ ’s)	151	153
1	10	Blockchain	Blockchain	NNP	compound	11	PERSON	 (NP (NNP Blockchain)	154	164
1	11	Joe	Joe	NNP	root	0	PERSON	 (NNP Joe)))	165	168
1	12	.	.	.	punct	11	O	 (. .)))	168	169

2	1	You	you	PRP	nsubj	4	O	 (ROOT (S (NP (PRP You))	171	174
2	2	can	can	MD	aux	4	O	 (VP (MD can)	175	178
2	3	not	not	RB	advmod	4	O	 (RB not)	178	181
2	4	regulate	regulate	VB	root	0	O	 (VP (VB regulate)	182	190
2	5	it	it	PRP	obj	4	O	 (NP (PRP it))))	191	193
2	6	.	.	.	punct	4	O	 (. .)))	193	194

