0	1	Sen.	Sen.	NNP	compound	2	O	 (ROOT (S (NP (NNP Sen.)	0	4
0	2	Manchin	Manchin	NNP	nsubj	3	PERSON	 (NNP Manchin))	5	12
0	3	Joins	join	VBZ	root	0	O	 (VP (VBZ Joins)	13	18
0	4	GOP	GOP	NNP	compound	5	ORGANIZATION	 (NP (NNP GOP)	19	22
0	5	Colleagues	colleague	NNS	obj	3	ORGANIZATION	 (NNS Colleagues))	23	33
0	6	in	in	IN	mark	7	O	 (PP (IN in)	34	36
0	7	Defeating	defeat	VBG	advcl	3	O	 (S (VP (VBG Defeating)	37	46
0	8	Abortion	abortion	NN	compound	11	O	 (NP (NN Abortion)	47	55
0	9	Bill	Bill	NNP	compound	10	PERSON	 (NML (NNP Bill)	56	60
0	10	Effing	Effing	NNP	compound	11	PERSON	 (NNP Effing))	62	68
0	11	ghouls	ghoul	NNS	obj	7	O	 (NNS ghouls))	69	75
0	12	pushing	push	VBG	advcl	7	O	 (S (VP (VBG pushing)	76	83
0	13	this	this	DT	det	14	O	 (NP (DT this)	84	88
0	14	bill	bill	NN	obj	12	O	 (NN bill))))))))	89	93
0	15	.	.	.	punct	3	O	 (. .)))	93	94

1	1	(	(	-LRB-	punct	2	O	 (ROOT (FRAG (NP (-LRB- -LRB-) (NN D) (-RRB- -RRB-)) (NP (NN emonic)) (. .)))	95	96
1	2	D	d	NN	root	0	O		96	97
1	3	)	)	-RRB-	punct	2	O		97	98
1	4	emonic	emonic	NN	dep	2	O		98	104
1	5	.	.	.	punct	2	O		104	105

