0	1	Being	be	VBG	aux:pass	2	O	 (ROOT (S (S (VP (VBG Being)	0	5
0	2	banned	ban	VBN	root	0	O	 (VP (VBN banned)	6	12
0	3	from	from	IN	case	4	O	 (PP (IN from)	13	17
0	4	Twitter	Twitter	NNP	obl	2	ORGANIZATION	 (NP (NNP Twitter))))))	18	25
0	5	and	and	CC	cc	7	ORGANIZATION	 (CC and)	26	29
0	6	Facebook	Facebook	NNP	compound	7	ORGANIZATION	 (S (NP (NP (NNP Facebook)	30	38
0	7	INCREASES	INCREASES	NNP	conj	2	O	 (NNP INCREASES))	39	48
0	8	someone	someone	NN	nmod:poss	10	O	 (NP (NP (NN someone)	49	56
0	9	's	's	POS	case	8	O	 (POS 's))	56	58
0	10	credibility	credibility	NN	dep	7	O	 (NN credibility)))	59	70
0	11	as	as	RB	advmod	12	O	 (ADVP (ADVP (RB as)	71	73
0	12	far	far	RB	advmod	7	O	 (RB far))	74	77
0	13	as	as	IN	mark	16	O	 (SBAR (IN as)	78	80
0	14	I	I	PRP	nsubj	16	O	 (S (NP (PRP I))	81	82
0	15	'm	be	VBP	cop	16	O	 (VP (VBP 'm)	82	84
0	16	concerned	concerned	JJ	advcl	12	O	 (ADJP (JJ concerned)))))))	85	94
0	17	.	.	.	punct	2	O	 (. .)))	94	95

1	1	They	they	PRP	nsubj	3	O	 (ROOT (S (S (NP (PRP They))	97	101
1	2	only	only	RB	advmod	3	O	 (ADVP (RB only))	102	106
1	3	go	go	VBP	ccomp	16	O	 (VP (VBP go)	107	109
1	4	after	after	IN	case	6	O	 (PP (IN after)	110	115
1	5	the	the	DT	det	6	O	 (NP (NP (DT the)	116	119
1	6	ones	one	NNS	obl	3	O	 (NNS ones))	120	124
1	7	who	who	WP	nsubj	9	O	 (SBAR (WHNP (WP who))	125	128
1	8	are	be	VBP	aux	9	O	 (S (VP (VBP are)	129	132
1	9	speaking	speak	VBG	acl:relcl	6	O	 (VP (VBG speaking)	133	141
1	10	pure	pure	JJ	amod	11	O	 (NP (JJ pure)	142	146
1	11	truth	truth	NN	obj	9	O	 (NN truth))))))))))	147	152
1	12	,	,	,	punct	16	O	 (, ,)	152	153
1	13	they	they	PRP	nsubj	16	O	 (NP (PRP they))	154	158
1	14	do	do	VBP	aux	16	O	 (VP (VBP do)	159	161
1	15	n't	not	RB	advmod	16	O	 (RB n't)	161	164
1	16	pay	pay	VB	root	0	O	 (VP (VB pay)	165	168
1	17	attention	attention	NN	obj	16	O	 (NP (NN attention))	169	178
1	18	to	to	IN	case	20	O	 (PP (IN to)	179	181
1	19	establishment	establishment	NN	compound	20	O	 (NP (NN establishment)	182	195
1	20	puppets	puppet	NNS	obl	16	O	 (NNS puppets)))))	196	203
1	21	.	.	.	punct	16	O	 (. .)))	203	204

2	1	This	this	DT	nsubj	2	O	 (ROOT (S (NP (DT This))	206	210
2	2	is	be	VBZ	root	0	O	 (VP (VBZ is)	211	213
2	3	why	why	WRB	advmod	15	O	 (SBAR (S (S (SBAR (WHADVP (WRB why))	214	217
2	4	Gaetz	Gaetz	NNP	compound	13	PERSON	 (S (NP (NNP Gaetz)	218	223
2	5	,	,	,	punct	4	O	 (, ,)	223	224
2	6	MTG	MTG	NNP	conj	4	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP MTG)	225	228
2	7	,	,	,	punct	4	O	 (, ,)	228	229
2	8	Boebert	Boebert	NNP	conj	4	PERSON	 (NNP Boebert)	230	237
2	9	,	,	,	punct	4	O	 (, ,)	237	238
2	10	Gosar	Gosar	NNP	conj	4	PERSON	 (NNP Gosar)	239	244
2	11	and	and	CC	cc	12	O	 (CC and)	245	248
2	12	Jim	Jim	NNP	conj	4	PERSON	 (NNP Jim)	249	252
2	13	Jordan	Jordan	NNP	nsubj	15	PERSON	 (NNP Jordan))	253	259
2	14	all	all	DT	advmod	15	O	 (ADVP (DT all))	260	263
2	15	have	have	VBP	advcl	25	O	 (VP (VBP have)	264	268
2	16	targets	target	NNS	obj	15	O	 (NP (NP (NNS targets))	269	276
2	17	painted	paint	VBN	acl	16	O	 (VP (VBN painted)	277	284
2	18	on	on	IN	case	19	O	 (PP (IN on)	285	287
2	19	them	they	PRP	obl	17	O	 (NP (PRP them))))))))	288	292
2	20	,	,	,	punct	25	O	 (, ,)	292	293
2	21	they	they	PRP	nsubj	25	O	 (NP (PRP they))	294	298
2	22	are	be	VBP	cop	25	O	 (VP (VBP are)	299	302
2	23	true	true	JJ	amod	25	O	 (NP (JJ true)	303	307
2	24	MAGA	MAGA	NNP	compound	25	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP MAGA)	308	312
2	25	patriots	patriot	NNS	dep	2	O	 (NNS patriots))))	313	321
2	26	instead	instead	RB	cc	29	O	 (CONJP (RB instead)	322	329
2	27	of	of	IN	fixed	26	O	 (IN of))	330	332
2	28	just	just	RB	advmod	29	O	 (S (ADVP (RB just))	333	337
2	29	swamp	swamp	VB	conj	25	O	 (VP (VB swamp)	338	343
2	30	creatures	creature	NNS	obj	29	O	 (NP (NNS creatures))	344	353
2	31	with	with	IN	case	34	O	 (PP (IN with)	354	358
2	32	an	a	DT	det	34	O	 (NP (DT an)	359	361
2	33	"	"	``	punct	34	O	 (`` ")	362	363
2	34	R	r	NN	obl	29	O	 (NN R)	363	364
2	35	"	"	''	punct	34	O	 ('' ")))	364	365
2	36	next	next	RB	advmod	29	O	 (ADVP (RB next)	366	370
2	37	to	to	IN	case	39	O	 (PP (IN to)	371	373
2	38	their	they	PRP$	nmod:poss	39	O	 (NP (PRP$ their)	374	379
2	39	names	name	NNS	obl	36	O	 (NNS names)))))))))	380	385
2	40	.	.	.	punct	2	O	 (. .)))	385	386

3	1	Matt	Matt	NNP	compound	2	PERSON	 (ROOT (S (NP (NNP Matt)	388	392
3	2	Gaetz	Gaetz	NNP	nsubj	5	PERSON	 (NNP Gaetz))	393	398
3	3	is	be	VBZ	cop	5	O	 (VP (VBZ is)	399	401
3	4	under	under	IN	case	5	O	 (PP (IN under)	402	407
3	5	trial	trial	NN	root	0	O	 (NP (NP (NN trial))	408	413
3	6	for	for	IN	case	10	O	 (PP (IN for)	414	417
3	7	child	child	NN	compound	9	O	 (NP (NML (NN child)	418	423
3	8	sex	sex	NN	compound	9	O	 (NN sex)	424	427
3	9	trafficking	trafficking	NN	compound	10	O	 (NN trafficking))	428	439
3	10	Pedo	Pedo	NNP	nmod	5	PERSON	 (NNP Pedo))))))))	441	445

