0	1	IDF	IDF	NNP	nsubj	2	ORGANIZATION	 (ROOT (S (NP (NNP IDF))	0	3
0	2	attacked	attack	VBD	root	0	O	 (VP (VBD attacked)	4	12
0	3	Palestinians	Palestinians	NNPS	obj	2	MISC	 (NP (NP (NNPS Palestinians))	13	25
0	4	and	and	CC	cc	5	O	 (CC and)	26	29
0	5	children	child	NNS	conj	3	O	 (NP (NNS children)))	30	38
0	6	at	at	IN	case	8	O	 (PP (IN at)	39	41
0	7	Demascus	Demascus	NNP	compound	8	LOCATION	 (NP (NNP Demascus)	42	50
0	8	Gate	Gate	NNP	obl	2	LOCATION	 (NNP Gate))))	51	55
0	9	.	.	.	punct	2	O	 (. .)))	55	56

1	1	Child	child	NN	nsubj	17	O	 (ROOT (S (S (NP (NP (NN Child))	57	62
1	2	hit	hit	VBN	acl	1	O	 (VP (VBN hit)	63	66
1	3	by	by	IN	case	7	O	 (PP (IN by)	67	69
1	4	stun	stun	NN	compound	7	O	 (NP (NP (NN stun)	70	74
1	5	grenade	grenade	NN	compound	7	O	 (NML (NN grenade)	75	82
1	6	*	*	SYM	dep	5	O	 (SYM *))	83	84
1	7	warning	warning	NN	obl	2	O	 (NN warning)	84	91
1	8	graphic	graphic	JJ	amod	7	O	 (JJ graphic))	92	99
1	9	*	*	NFP	punct	7	O	 (NFP *)	99	100
1	10	Russian	russian	JJ	amod	11	NATIONALITY	 (NP (NP (JJ Russian)	102	109
1	11	dictator	dictator	NN	dep	7	TITLE	 (NN dictator))	110	118
1	12	sponsored	sponsor	VBN	acl	11	O	 (VP (VBN sponsored)	119	128
1	13	by	by	IN	case	15	O	 (PP (IN by)	129	131
1	14	crony	crony	JJ	amod	15	O	 (NP (JJ crony)	132	137
1	15	capitalism	capitalism	NN	obl	12	IDEOLOGY	 (NN capitalism)))))))))	138	148
1	16	is	be	VBZ	aux	17	O	 (VP (VBZ is)	149	151
1	17	bombing	bomb	VBG	root	0	O	 (VP (VBG bombing)	152	159
1	18	Freedom	Freedom	NNP	compound	19	LOCATION	 (NP (NP (NNP Freedom)	160	167
1	19	Square	Square	NNP	obj	17	LOCATION	 (NNP Square))	168	174
1	20	in	in	IN	case	21	O	 (PP (IN in)	175	177
1	21	Kharkiv	Kharkiv	NNP	nmod	19	LOCATION	 (NP (NNP Kharkiv))))	178	185
1	22	with	with	IN	case	23	O	 (PP (IN with)	186	190
1	23	dozens	dozen	NNS	obl	17	O	 (NP (NP (NNS dozens))	191	197
1	24	of	of	IN	case	26	O	 (PP (IN of)	198	200
1	25	civilian	civilian	JJ	amod	26	O	 (NP (JJ civilian)	201	209
1	26	casualties	casualty	NNS	nmod	23	O	 (NNS casualties))))))))	210	220
1	27	,	,	,	punct	17	O	 (, ,)	220	221
1	28	and	and	CC	cc	34	O	 (CC and)	222	225
1	29	suddenly	suddenly	RB	advmod	34	O	 (S (ADVP (RB suddenly))	226	234
1	30	"	"	``	punct	31	O	 (NP (`` ")	235	236
1	31	socialists	socialist	NNS	nsubj:pass	34	O	 (NNS socialists)	236	246
1	32	"	"	''	punct	31	O	 ('' "))	246	247
1	33	are	be	VBP	aux:pass	34	O	 (VP (VBP are)	248	251
1	34	outraged	outrage	VBN	conj	17	O	 (VP (VBN outraged)	252	260
1	35	by	by	IN	case	37	O	 (PP (IN by)	261	263
1	36	Jerusalem	Jerusalem	NNP	compound	37	CITY	 (NP (NNP Jerusalem)	264	273
1	37	police	police	NN	obl	34	O	 (NN police))))))	274	280
1	38	.	.	.	punct	17	O	 (. .)))	280	281

