0	1	He	he	PRP	nsubj:pass	6	O	 (ROOT (S (NP (PRP He))	0	2
0	2	's	be	VBZ	aux:pass	6	O	 (VP (VBZ 's)	2	4
0	3	always	always	RB	advmod	6	O	 (ADVP (RB always))	5	11
0	4	been	be	VBN	cop	6	O	 (VP (VBN been)	12	16
0	5	the	the	DT	det	6	O	 (NP (NP (DT the)	17	20
0	6	guy	guy	NN	root	0	O	 (NN guy))	21	24
0	7	that	that	WDT	nsubj	8	O	 (SBAR (WHNP (WDT that))	25	29
0	8	challenges	challenge	VBZ	acl:relcl	6	O	 (S (VP (VBZ challenges)	30	40
0	9	the	the	DT	det	10	O	 (NP (DT the)	41	44
0	10	man	man	NN	obj	8	O	 (NN man))))))))	45	48
0	11	.	.	.	punct	6	O	 (. .)))	48	49

1	1	Now	now	RB	advmod	4	DATE	 (ROOT (S (ADVP (RB Now))	50	53
1	2	he	he	PRP	nsubj:pass	4	O	 (NP (PRP he))	54	56
1	3	's	be	VBZ	aux:pass	4	O	 (VP (VBZ 's)	56	58
1	4	become	become	VBN	root	0	O	 (VP (VBN become)	59	65
1	5	such	such	PDT	det:predet	7	O	 (NP (PDT such)	66	70
1	6	a	a	DT	det	7	O	 (DT a)	71	72
1	7	shill	shill	NN	xcomp	4	O	 (NN shill))	73	78
1	8	for	for	IN	case	10	O	 (PP (IN for)	79	82
1	9	Big	big	JJ	amod	10	O	 (NP (NP (JJ Big)	83	86
1	10	Government	government	NN	obl	4	O	 (NN Government))	87	97
1	11	and	and	CC	cc	13	O	 (CC and)	98	101
1	12	Big	big	JJ	amod	13	ORGANIZATION	 (NP (JJ Big)	102	105
1	13	Pharma	Pharma	NNP	conj	10	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP Pharma))))))	106	112
1	14	.	.	.	punct	4	O	 (. .)))	112	113

2	1	And	and	CC	cc	5	O	 (ROOT (SBARQ (S (CC And)	114	117
2	2	people	people	NNS	nsubj	5	O	 (NP (NNS people))	118	124
2	3	have	have	VBP	aux	5	O	 (VP (VBP have)	125	129
2	4	been	be	VBN	aux	5	O	 (VP (VBN been)	130	134
2	5	asking	ask	VBG	dep	13	O	 (VP (VBG asking)	135	141
2	6	over	over	IN	case	10	O	 (PP (IN over)	142	146
2	7	the	the	DT	det	10	DURATION	 (NP (DT the)	147	150
2	8	past	past	JJ	amod	10	DATE	 (JJ past)	151	155
2	9	two	two	CD	nummod	10	DATE	 (CD two)	156	159
2	10	years	year	NNS	obl	5	DATE	 (NNS years)))))))	160	165
2	11	,	,	,	punct	13	O	 (, ,)	165	166
2	12	what	what	WP	nsubj	13	O	 (WHNP (WP what))	167	171
2	13	happened	happen	VBD	root	0	O	 (SQ (VP (VBD happened)	172	180
2	14	to	to	IN	case	16	O	 (PP (IN to)	181	183
2	15	Howard	Howard	NNP	compound	16	PERSON	 (NP (NNP Howard)	184	190
2	16	Stern	Stern	NNP	obl	13	PERSON	 (NNP Stern)))))	191	196
2	17	?	?	.	punct	13	O	 (. ?)))	196	197

3	1	SS	ss	NN	root	0	O	 (ROOT (FRAG (NP (NN SS))	199	201
3	2	:	:	:	punct	1	O	 (: :)	201	202
3	3	Howard	Howard	NNP	compound	4	PERSON	 (S (NP (NNP Howard)	204	210
3	4	Stern	Stern	NNP	nsubj	5	PERSON	 (NNP Stern))	211	216
3	5	needs	need	VBZ	appos	1	O	 (VP (VBZ needs)	217	222
3	6	these	these	DT	det	7	O	 (NP (DT these)	223	228
3	7	asskickings	asskicking	NNS	obj	5	O	 (NNS asskickings))))	229	240
3	8	.	.	.	punct	1	O	 (. .)))	240	241

