0	1	Biden	Biden	NNP	compound	2	ORGANIZATION	 (ROOT (S (NP (NP (NNP Biden)	0	5
0	2	Admin	Admin	NNP	nsubj	6	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP Admin))	6	11
0	3	Rips	Rips	NNP	compound	4	ORGANIZATION	 (NP (NNP Rips)	12	16
0	4	Florida	Florida	NNP	dep	2	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP Florida)))	17	24
0	5	,	,	,	punct	6	O	 (, ,)	24	25
0	6	Suggests	suggest	VBZ	root	0	O	 (VP (VBZ Suggests)	26	34
0	7	Feds	Feds	NNPS	compound	10	O	 (NP (NP (NNPS Feds)	35	39
0	8	Will	Will	NNP	compound	10	O	 (NNP Will)	40	44
0	9	Crack	Crack	NNP	compound	10	O	 (NNP Crack)	45	50
0	10	Down	Down	NNP	obj	6	O	 (NNP Down))	51	55
0	11	For	for	IN	case	15	O	 (SBAR (S (S (PP (IN For)	56	59
0	12	Barring	bar	VBG	case	15	O	 (PP (VBG Barring)	60	67
0	13	Sexual	sexual	JJ	amod	15	O	 (NP (JJ Sexual)	68	74
0	14	Orientation	orientation	NN	compound	15	O	 (NN Orientation)	75	86
0	15	Discussions	discussion	NNS	obl	24	O	 (NNS Discussions))))	87	98
0	16	In	in	IN	case	17	O	 (PP (IN In)	99	101
0	17	Grades	grade	NNS	obl	24	O	 (NP (NNS Grades)))	102	108
0	18	K	k	CD	nummod	20	NUMBER	 (NP (NP (CD K)	109	110
0	19	-	-	SYM	dep	20	NUMBER	 (SYM -)	110	111
0	20	3	3	CD	nsubj	24	NUMBER	 (CD 3))	111	112
0	21	The	the	DT	det	22	O	 (NP (DT The)	114	117
0	22	pedos	pedo	NNS	dep	20	O	 (NNS pedos)))	118	123
0	23	are	be	VBP	aux	24	O	 (VP (VBP are)	124	127
0	24	going	go	VBG	acl:relcl	10	O	 (VP (VBG going)	128	133
0	25	to	to	TO	mark	27	O	 (S (VP (TO to)	134	136
0	26	be	be	VB	aux	27	O	 (VP (VB be)	137	139
0	27	coming	come	VBG	xcomp	24	O	 (VP (VBG coming)	140	146
0	28	out	out	RP	compound:prt	27	O	 (PRT (RP out))	147	150
0	29	in	in	IN	case	31	O	 (PP (IN in)	151	153
0	30	full	full	JJ	amod	31	O	 (NP (JJ full)	154	158
0	31	force	force	NN	obl	27	O	 (NN force))))))))))	159	164
0	32	but	but	CC	cc	36	O	 (CC but)	165	168
0	33	they	they	PRP	nsubj	36	O	 (S (NP (PRP they))	169	173
0	34	will	will	MD	aux	36	O	 (VP (MD will)	174	178
0	35	have	have	VB	aux	36	O	 (VP (VB have)	179	183
0	36	met	meet	VBN	conj	24	O	 (VP (VBN met)	184	187
0	37	their	they	PRP$	nmod:poss	38	O	 (NP (PRP$ their)	188	193
0	38	match	match	NN	obj	36	O	 (NN match))	194	199
0	39	in	in	IN	case	40	O	 (PP (IN in)	200	202
0	40	DeSantis	DeSantis	NNP	obl	36	PERSON	 (NP (NNP DeSantis)))))))))))	203	211
0	41	.	.	.	punct	6	O	 (. .)))	211	212

