0	1	January	January	NNP	compound	4	DATE	 (ROOT (S (NP (NNP January)	0	7
0	2	6	6	CD	nummod	3	DATE	 (NML (CD 6)	8	9
0	3	committee	committee	NN	compound	4	O	 (NN committee))	10	19
0	4	member	member	NN	nsubj	5	O	 (NN member))	20	26
0	5	says	say	VBZ	root	0	O	 (VP (VBZ says)	27	31
0	6	Trump	Trump	NNP	nsubj	10	PERSON	 (S (NP (NNP Trump)	32	37
0	7	'	'	POS	case	6	O	 (POS '))	38	39
0	8	absolutely	absolutely	RB	advmod	10	O	 (VP (VP (ADVP (RB absolutely)	39	49
0	9	'	'	''	punct	8	O	 ('' '))	49	50
0	10	tampering	tamper	VBG	ccomp	5	O	 (VBG tampering)	51	60
0	11	with	with	IN	case	12	O	 (PP (IN with)	61	65
0	12	witnesses	witness	NNS	obl	10	O	 (NP (NNS witnesses)))	66	75
0	13	....	....	,	punct	10	O	 (, ....)	77	81
0	14	bunch	bunch	NN	nsubj	18	O	 (S (NP (NP (NN bunch))	81	86
0	15	of	of	IN	case	17	O	 (PP (IN of)	87	89
0	16	Trump	Trump	NNP	compound	17	ORGANIZATION	 (NP (NNP Trump)	90	95
0	17	Derangement	Derangement	NNP	nmod	14	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP Derangement))))	96	107
0	18	Hate	hate	VB	ccomp	10	ORGANIZATION	 (VP (VB Hate)	108	112
0	19	-	-	HYPH	punct	18	ORGANIZATION	 (HYPH -)	112	113
0	20	mongers	monger	NNS	obj	18	ORGANIZATION	 (NP (NNS mongers)))))	113	120
0	21	,	,	,	punct	10	O	 (, ,)	120	121
0	22	that	that	WDT	nsubj	25	O	 (SBAR (WHNP (WDT that))	122	126
0	23	ca	can	MD	aux	25	O	 (S (VP (MD ca)	127	129
0	24	n't	not	RB	advmod	25	O	 (RB n't)	129	132
0	25	see	see	VB	ccomp	10	O	 (VP (VB see)	133	136
0	26	past	past	IN	case	32	DATE	 (PP (IN past)	137	141
0	27	their	they	PRP$	nmod:poss	32	O	 (NP (PRP$ their)	142	147
0	28	own	own	JJ	amod	32	O	 (JJ own)	148	151
0	29	self	self	NN	obl	31	O	 (ADJP (NN self)	152	156
0	30	-	-	HYPH	punct	31	O	 (HYPH -)	156	157
0	31	consuming	consume	VBG	amod	32	O	 (VBG consuming))	157	166
0	32	hatred	hatred	NN	obl	25	O	 (NN hatred))))))))))	167	173
0	33	.	.	.	punct	5	O	 (. .)))	173	174

