0	1	Biden	Biden	NNP	nsubj	2	PERSON	 (ROOT (S (NP (NNP Biden))	0	5
0	2	Weighs	weigh	VBZ	root	0	O	 (VP (VBZ Weighs)	6	12
0	3	Deploying	deploy	VBG	xcomp	2	O	 (S (VP (VBG Deploying)	13	22
0	4	Thousands	thousand	NNS	obj	3	O	 (NP (NP (NNS Thousands))	23	32
0	5	of	of	IN	case	6	O	 (PP (IN of)	33	35
0	6	Troops	troops	NNS	nmod	4	O	 (NP (NNS Troops))))	36	42
0	7	to	to	IN	case	9	O	 (PP (IN to)	43	45
0	8	Eastern	Eastern	NNP	compound	9	LOCATION	 (NP (NP (NNP Eastern)	46	53
0	9	Europe	Europe	NNP	obl	3	LOCATION	 (NNP Europe))	54	60
0	10	and	and	CC	cc	12	O	 (CC and)	61	64
0	11	Baltics	Baltics	NNP	compound	12	PERSON	 (NP (NNP Baltics)	65	72
0	12	Dude	dude	NN	conj	9	PERSON	 (NN Dude))))	74	78
0	13	,	,	,	punct	3	O	 (, ,)	78	79
0	14	fuck	fuck	VB	dep	3	O	 (S (VP (VB fuck)	80	84
0	15	this	this	DT	det	16	O	 (NP (DT this)	85	89
0	16	shit	shit	NN	obj	14	O	 (NN shit))	90	94
0	17	so	so	RB	advmod	18	O	 (ADVP (RB so)	95	97
0	18	hard	hard	RB	advmod	14	O	 (RB hard)))))))	98	102
0	19	.	.	.	punct	2	O	 (. .)))	102	103

1	1	What	what	WDT	dep	5	O	 (ROOT (SBAR (WHNP (WDT What))	104	108
1	2	a	a	DT	det	5	O	 (S (NP (DT a)	109	110
1	3	completely	completely	RB	advmod	4	O	 (ADJP (RB completely)	111	121
1	4	incompetent	incompetent	JJ	amod	5	O	 (JJ incompetent))	122	133
1	5	asshole	asshole	NN	root	0	O	 (NN asshole)))	134	141
1	6	.	.	.	punct	5	O	 (. .)))	141	142

